Opinions are free, which is why we're
here. It's news and talk that our
sponsors agree on.
WCTR. Up next, it's Area 53 and Marvin
Trill, broadcasting live from his trailer
in the desert. A new planet found in
space. Is it really a planet or a decoy
put up to confuse us? Ghosts, time travel,
and the flushing toilet: which way did
Newton's toilet spiral? And finally, are
women made from sand? We explore deeper
and get to the truth. I'm Marvin Trill, this
is Area 53. Hello, you're on the line. Yeah,
hi, I'm a truck driver and listen to your
show all the time. I see a lot of
unexplained phenomena out there,
especially in restrooms. I agree with you
about the moon. We never landed on the
moon. It's such a good fake. Remember the
Russians, our arch-enemy, still I might
add, them and the Australians and some
species of dog, they beat us into space.
The only thing the Russians are shooting
into space are hot dogs and monkeys, kind
of a Noah's Ark fast-food kind of vibe. Hey, my
dad alone could make a better space station
than them. Intriguing. I'd like to meet
her. On the conspiracy line, caller, you're
in Area 53. Do not use fluoride, it's
evil! It made me kill my doctor. Why would
we worry about a chemical that the
government puts into the water? Animals
can now be trained to fly, including
several species of bird. Think about the
military applications. Hello, caller. Hi, my
name's Emmanuel. I'm really worried about
hackers sending a nuclear bomb after me,
you know, through the phones. Do you think
they can pinpoint my location? Look, it's
good for the economy to live in constant
fear. I mean, the phone company, they have
your name on the bill, they know your
number. How do you feel about that? I knew
it! Hello, Julie from Liberty City, you're
on the line. A cowboy ghost has been
haunting my house. I want you to take off
your blouse, stand at the window, stand
there for hours each night, lure him in.
Trapping rogue spirits is dangerous work,
especially topless. Take lots of
Photographs, all right. Who's got a theory
for me next? "Hey man, love the show, but
when are you guys going to start seeing
the bigger picture? We've been lied to,
man, and guys like you don't help much,
you know. You're virtually one of them
soon. You know what I'm talking about." If
people could please just attempt to make
sense, that's all I'm asking. Last night,
as I was laying in my pod meditating, and
it occurred to me: why are you even
listening to me? Turn off all electrical
devices, including your radio! Hector in
San Fierro, why are you still listening?
"Because I was hoping you could explain these
noises." "What noises? God, not you two now!"
Think about the things we talked about
today. Think seriously. Think: can it be
real? Can it be false? We'll see you next
time in Area 53. Be careful out there,
wherever you
are. That was Area 53. We're sorry.
Sometimes the law is not enough. "Did you
file this opinion in the McPherson case?" "No,
it wasn't urgent. I filed an A-440." "An A-440?" "I
know, I know. So I went shopping for these
loafers." "Has anyone got a stapler?" "Got a
lot of forms and there's a slight breeze
in here." Because paperwork is dramatic.
Catch it Thursdays on Weazel before it
catches you. Next up on WCTR: the news. We
try to make it interesting and not
depressing. This... this is Lianne for WCTR
News. Foreigners are coming. Who are they
and why should we care? The FDA warns
shampoo is killing your unborn child.
Plus, protests continue outside the Zebra
Bar Candy Company. Now for Traffic and
Transit with Richard Burns. "That's right,
Lianne, I'm Richard Burns. The aftermath of
the devastating earthquake continues.
Travel is still severely restricted
statewide. Officials say there are still
no reported casualties, which is truly
unfortunate, as it makes for incredibly
boring news. The federal government is
still refusing aid to help rebuild
bridges, and everyone is blaming each
other. The governor is threatening to
bomb Australia, despite scientific proof...
It wasn't their fault. Richard Burns...
WCTR Police say gang trouble is on the
rise again, especially in Los Santos.
Sources believe it is linked to the
rising drug trade, while others blame
the fascist pigs. Also in gang news,
Customs officials report a huge influx
of Russian mobsters and cheap weapons
since the fall of the Wall. The
governor's office said everything is
okay. In Vinewood news, rapper Madd Dogg was
celebrating the launch of his new
clothing line. Richard caught up with him.
"The thing about Madd Dogg is I'm thinking
about becoming a superstar. I mean, you
know, I've done everything I could do in
the rap game. I won, shit, hands down, nobody
can handle me, you know? Lifetime champ. No
shit, can I say shit? Oh, hey, man, it's cool,
that's cool, okay. No shit, I got clothes, I
got labels coming out, you know what I'm
saying? I'm doing drinks, I got shoes,
tires, rims. Thinking, you know, next stage
is being a full-on superstar. You... I get
to wear a tight suit and nail a lot of
tail, you dig? You know what I do in real
life. Got to get me a drink, though, right
now, 'cause I'm thirsty." You know what a
troubled man sounds like. He should lay
off the sauce. Also today, a Tourette's
theater group banned from the park
unless they take up mime. And finally, in
foreign news, a suspected U.S. agent was
caught in Panama selling weaponry to
right-wing guerrillas, causing a major
incident, but plan mostly to gloss over
the implications and hope you enjoy some
sporting activity tonight. The State
Department is advising against foreign
travel. This was Lianne Forget, WCTR News. Let's
be careful out there. Up next on WCTR, it's
the man coaches hate. It's Derrick Thackery in
The Tight End Zone, brought to you by Eris
Pump-Up shoes, because women love a winner
and winners wear shoes. Should we, uh,
start with the national
anthem? Yeah, screw it. Yeah, I got—I got
too drunk last night. Just, uh, play the
opening
music. Welcome back to The Tight End Zone. Now,
It's time for something really important:
fat men talking about games they don't
really understand, played by people they
don't know. I'm your host, Derrick
Thackery. What a crazy year it's been! Let's
recap: drug scandals involving preschool
soccer
moms, woo! And the National Finals, rich
and popular people are fighting it out,
pay attention. The country is in
mourning, and most importantly, sports,
where we talk to a fitness expert
about the crucial role of endorsed
clothing. And who could forget, we visit
the greatest
moments. Here he comes! He's in the
shadows... there he is! Is he going to make
it? Yes, he did! Ladies and gentlemen, what
you have just witnessed is the biggest
moment in world history! Who cares about
a Declaration of Independence or
discovery of penicillin? You have just
seen one man score a point! When the rest
of the world discovers TV, they'll be
able to see this! Wow, isn't that amazing?
He did what he was paid to do. We love
sports more than you. Love it or loathe it,
let's talk about it. Stay in The Tight
End
Zone. Let's go to the
phones. "Yeah, the Wolves!" Hey Derrick, my name
is Jason, and I'm a Wolves fan. First-time
caller. I don't vote, I can't be bothered,
but I will kick your ass if you
disrespect my sports team. Okay, the
Wolves, that's a team playing sports as
if they cared. "Yeah, the Wolves!" I don't
care who's sleeping with who on the team.
Yeah, I'm with you, buddy. Okay, hey, let's
take another call. Who's on the phone?
Hello caller, you're on with the tight end
of radio. Hey, I'm a big Olympics fan,
always have been since day one, been to
every one. Me too, I love the Games,
especially the
luge. I'm married, so, uh, sliding down an icy
tunnel of doom at high speed makes sense.
Yeah, I know about frigid action myself. I
mean, they've got to be kidding me! Since
when has running been an Olympic sport?
Running ain't a sport! Don't make me puke.
Anyone can run! My ex-wife made me an
athlete. I ran my ass off when the Red
Baron flew into town, I tell you! When I
was a kid, there were only three sports
that mattered: football, baseball, and
killing Communists. And, uh, I had a great
childhood, really great, even if my uncle
did come into my room that late at night,
drunk, and... oh, that was nuts. Anyway,
look who's on the line. We got a
Caledonians fan on the line. Tough times,
huh? Hey, uh, your whole life revolving
around rich men playing poorly? Man, I
totally identify with shallow heroes who
I don't know personally. God, I love a
dude with a big pituitary gland. I love
the Callie, man, but you know this year,
I'm telling you, they're going to need to
score some points and get some yardage
and win the game. Yeah, if they don't win,
men will be beating their wives with
good reason. Hey, they got to start
playing to win, trying to score some on
the other team. I wish I had a wife so
she could beat me. Here's what I say, man:
if you want to be number one, you got to
go for first place. I know, I know. Hey, I
mean, uh, you know, it's great stating the
obvious, but once you get paid for it,
things get really complicated, man. I was
at their training camp this spring, and
the mood in the locker room, dude...
Guys were getting changed, man. I mean,
they were really getting prepared. Shoes
were going on feet, shirts were going on
the shirt part of their body, serious
faces on them, and you could tell that
they were going to play this game. Bottom
line is, if they don't score more points
than the other team, they can't win. Yeah,
man. God, you have some spooky insights
into sports, dude. I love your show, man. I—
I love
you. Yeah, look, great talking to you.
Excuse me. Hey, that's really perceptive
stuff. You know, we've been petitioning
stadiums to install a urinal trough in
front of each row of seats. Now, it's so
inconvenient having to leave your seat.
Make everyone stand up. "Get up! Get up!" You
know, to... to let you by, then go stand in
line for the bathroom. I mean, half the
time, we can barely walk anyway. All right,
so we'll be handing out petitions that
say, "Support the team, don't leave the
game, pee at your seat!" Go to the phones. I'm
a big fight fan, love a bit of a punch-up.
Since my wife and children got taken
into a shelter, my friend said, "Chuck, you
obviously love hitting things," so I've
gotten into boxing. How about that fight
between Gonzalez and Jackson? Well,
there's one thing about boxing I always
remember, you know: one man wins, the other
goes home a loser. Because in boxing,
unlike most sports, gravity works
downwards. You've got to be fucking me! Hey,
Derrick, there... don't shit on no one, but, uh, I
do like to piss on my seat, and, uh, at my
seat too, not really on it, so stay out of
the way. Tell me the fight game: that ain't
rigged, is it? Of course not! Hey, how could
anything professional be fake? Hey,
there's too much money at stake, for one
thing. I mean, these guys got too much to
lose. I mean, why is a guy going to take a
dive for a few extra million when he
could earn that over a number of years
getting his brain turned to pulp? Be
serious for a minute! The clock is
counting down again. It's time for Derrick
to head to the locker room and celebrate
in the shower with... We'll see you next
time. Bring a cooler full of beers and
get ready to riot! This has been The
Tight End
Zone! And this is WCTR, proving that radio
is better than TV. That's the show men
with large guts love. Deal with your
ignorance in one minute flat. Complex
issues in 60 seconds.
WCTR. Coming up next, the most mind-numbing
thing since the lobotomy: Entertaining
America. This week on Entertaining
America: Richard Goblin — one man's
triumphant return to fucking! The Sherman
Octuplets: a venturous man says he's
slept with them all. Plus noise, speed,
danger, cursing, and patriotism! Finally,
Come together this weekend at the All-
American Drunk Driving Cup! Hi from
Vinewood, you're on Entertaining America
with me, Billy Dexter, bringing you
everything that is important in culture
and entertainment, if there is a
difference between the... From the heart of
entertainment in America, Vinewood, San
Andreas, you're with me, the Dex! Wanted to
call the show Stack the De— but not yet,
*cough*. Anyway, great big show for you this
week! Controversy! They'll be giving me a
Pulitzer! Anyway, today we've got some
great guests. First up, we speak to
troubled action hero Jack Howitzer. Then
we have a live phone link-up with a very
special guest: modern-day Lazarus, a man
back from the grave, now making it as an
extra in major motion pictures. Then I
will explain the secrets of the universe
to everyone. But first up, Stack the Decks,
in which I, Billy Dexter, meet the
entertainers in the news.
*Cough*. Jack Howitzer, once the biggest star
in America, but the last three years have
been unkind. People describe him as a
dinosaur, an action hero relic from the
'80s, a musclebound Neanderthal, and my
favorite, "the most stupid gorilla in the
jungle." Jack, welcome to the show. *Cough*. Good
to be here, Dex, pleasure. Yeah, so
your movies, Exploder and Annihilator,
got America through some tough times, and
I was also a huge fan of... of '0 Seconds to
Death'. Thank... thank you. But many say
your new film has gone too far. No, this
is a romantic comedy with drama. It's got
action, it's got a heart. That's what's
most important, I think. Okay, well, let's
take a listen to the trailer. All right,
let's roll.
"...that he was a man at war with himself,
fighting a war that someone else lost."
"It's over, Tim! The war's over!" "It's never
over!"
You've seen him wipe out millions of
Cambodians in Exploder. Now Jack Howitzer
is Tim in his most challenging role yet.
"We're here, Tim. A preschool for slow
children. You're the new teacher, Tim."
Special Needs Cop. It's the story of a
psychotic ex-Marine showing tough love to
special-ed kids. "One of you tards has been
running Peruvian flake through the
special-ed school, and I'm going to find
it! No juice and cookies, motherfuckers!" But
soon, he becomes one of them. "What is this?"
"That's teacher's gun. You want to see
it?" "Oh, you went and shot yourself! Way to
go!" He was finally beginning to live a
normal life, then all hell breaks loose!
"Timmy, you're so stupid, you count with your
fingers! You want to party with me? Bring
it on!" "Damn, what are you doing?" "I fought
for my country! Welcome to the land of
freedom,
motherfucker!" Special Needs Cop. He had a lot
to learn. This film cannot be rated. "Wow,
that's terrible. No wonder our studios
are surrounded by protesters." "How could
anybody find that offensive?" "No, no, Jack,
it's appalling. Your insensitive
portrayal of disabled people makes me
physically sick! And the idea of you
calling someone slow-witted is, frankly,
laughable." "Hold on, hold on. Drugs are a
problem throughout all of society, and I
fight them by any means necessary." "But
you use drugs." "No, no, no! I'd rather die
than use drugs! I use steroids and some
recreational blow, but I got the funds
for it, you know. I got the money." "Yeah.
Don't you think you're just a little out
of touch?" "Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Yeah, I'm
rich, and I work in Vinewood, okay? I'm not
out of touch. Action, weightlifting, and
killing foreigners — that never goes out
of style, Dex! My last film, okay, Loincloth,
about a wrestler who's dropped
into Thailand, and I saved the world by
teabagging the bad guys! That's a
spiritual picture. That's love! Teabagging —
that stuff ain't out of style!" "Yeah,
things are more sensitive now." "I was
affected, all right? When Hooch got hurt in
Exploder, I mean, I — I thought it was time
to do something, a film that made a
difference." "Yeah, but Hooch was a character.
Exploder was a movie." "Right, right, and I
was there, and I should have killed them!"
Aw, don't push me, Dex! I'll give you a
war you won't believe! That look in your
eye, right here, right now, okay? Oh, Jack...
Jack, all I'm saying is you launching
missiles from a special wheelchair and
killing innocent civilians is somewhat
insensitive. There's never any innocent
civilians in life! If the Reds roll down
the street right now, what are you going
to do? The Reds lost, man! It's—it's over.
You can come home. I'll shoot those
bastards with this: The Family Killer!
Jack! Jack, put that away, please! What, this?
It's a submachine gun! Come on, it's not
serious. Oh, but you're Billy Dexter. Who
put you up to this? Gorbachev? No, no, you
should calm down. I heard what you said
about me! You think steroids shrank my genitals!
No, no, put the gun down, please! I'm—I'm
sure you have huge ones! Please, stop! Come
on, they haven't shrunk! Touch them! Feel
them! Come on, sniff them! Do something!
Touch them! Touch them or die! They're
still big! Oh God, they're huge, Jack! Yeah!
Ma—m—don't grab 'em like that! Oh, boy, I
was kidding! What are you, a boyfriend of
mine or something? Hey, hey, hey, you had
me scared there for a minute. I—I—I—I
crapped myself! Take it easy, it's not
even loaded!
Oh! Oh, Dex! Oh, shit! Oh well, I guess it was.
Oh, okay, Billy, don't fool around! Get up,
boy! Get up, come on! Damn it, his brain is
leaking! Help! Oh, there's only one thing
to do: I got to defend freedom! No time to
cry, only time to die! Welcome to the land
of freedom!
Shit! That was Entertaining America,
showing you why America is so respected
culturally across the world. Prepare to
be scared. The news is
next. This is Lianne for WCTR News. Pop
sensation Crow threatens to stop singing;
America celebrates! And movies: are they
true? Plus, children: was Freud right? Do
they want us all dead? Now, a WCTR
exclusive with Richard Burns.
That's right, Lianne. I'm Richard Burns. Crime in
Los Santos has skyrocketed, with
officials saying carjacking, murder...
Robbery and gang activity is all on the
rise. Police described it as, and I'm
quoting here, "nothing to worry about." I
met up with a real-life carjacker
earlier who showed me the ropes. I call
it the three G's: you just grab, get in, and
go. "Oh my God, you're in so much trouble!"
"You shut up, [__]! Yeah, you be quiet,
[__]! This is a news story." "Oh, cool! This
is great, this is quality journalism. Uh,
back to you, Leanne." "Hey, let's get blunted
and grab some Cluckin' Bell. I have got
mad munchies." "Sounds good to me, fire it
up, dude. You got any papers?" Youth
counselors in Los Santos are heading to
the streets and meeting one-on-one with
members of the community. One citizen
told WCTR the real problem with drugs:
"They're always saying it's too many drugs
in the hood, homie. That's [__] plain
[__]. I mean, way I see it is, it ain't
enough drugs in the hood. Ain't nothing
like enough, and that's the real problem
for people." Police still have no leads in
the tragic murder of Officer Ralph
Pendlebury, whose body was found recently.
Pendlebury worked for Internal Affairs.
It was believed he was close to
uncovering a huge corruption ring within
the LSPD. A police spokesman denied the
story. A San Fierro man is suing the
Renaissance Fair for selling him replica
weaponry, which he blames for a string of
murders. Richard caught up with him. "I
purchased a working catapult at the
Renaissance Fair, and after a fight with
my insurance salesman over my DWI, I
began lobbing balls of fire at his house
and burnt down an entire neighborhood.
It's inexcusable! The manufacturers will
pay. Give me some money! Come on, give me
some money! It's their fault! What kind of
a person sells a catapult without
putting a very clear warning on the side?
I don't want to work very hard, so I've
hired a lawyer. I'm going to be rich!"
Seems fair enough to me. I'm Leanne Forget,
that was the news. Be safe out
[Music]
there. "Hello? Uh, Mom, it's me, Jimmy. How
Great to hear from you. How are you? Not
good, Mom, I killed a man drunk driving. I
need bail money bad. Oh, can you, uh,
remortgage the house? Every day is
Mother's Day. San Andreas Telephone, for
those difficult conversations. Have you
heard the number one gardening show in
San Andreas? If not, here's what you're
missing: "Well, why don't you just go buy
your vegetables at the grocery store
then, you sycophants? God, I just don't
understand people! You go to hell!" "Well,
screw you too, my man. See if you're ever on
the show again. Next caller, hello." "Yeah,
what's that plant that blooms every 12
years, is eight feet high, and smells like hell? I
want to plant one on my ex-wife's lawn."
"It's called Amorphophallus
titanum. God, I love to say that...
Amorphophallus
titanum. And the sound of it gives me a
redwood in my khakis. If I come back as a
superhero, I want to be called that. It's
Amorphophallus titanum, the rare botanical
wonder. See his eight-foot erection as he
pollinates on everyone." "But why does it
sting so bad?" "It's about marking your
territory, my man. You don't mark your
territory, do you? You should try it. Pee
on the front door of your office, just
see if anybody thinks of coming near you."
"Okay, I-- I'll-- I would try that. Thank you
so much for the advice, Maurice." "Oh, I'm
here to help, sailor." Gardening with
Maurice, only on
WCTR. In darkness, you only have your
nocturnal instincts to rely on. Ultimate
in the Dark, the electric, stimulating new
game that's sweeping San Fierro. It's a
non-contact contact sport where you
throw a flying disc in the dark. "I got it!
Get him! Nail his ass!" It's a new
competitive sport for the uncompetitive,
an aggressive, action-packed game for
those who love nature and living on the
edge. It's harder than football, it's
faster than rugby. It's about throwing a
plastic disc and catching it. Pitch, then
catch, run to the goal, and score! Ultimate
Disc in the Dark, just like a real sport.
Only we made it up, and it has a great
social side. "Oh my God! What team are you
on?" "I'm on the other team!" "Me too!" "Take
that, silly!" But if you catch it, you've got
to know what to do with it. Some will
struggle, some will submit, everyone is
laughing, but it's your quest to come out
on top. This is a great excuse for some
serious fun and a way to meet people
like you, and never see them again. League
games begin at sunset every night in San
Fierro Civic Park, or start your own game.
And because it's night, it's not too
embarrassing to play a strip version.
Come and play Ultimate Disc in the Dark.
Talk is cheap, especially on this station,
featuring more rich, angry people
complaining.
WCTR. Do you find your daughter's friends
attractive, but know they look at you as
just a dad? Does the typing pool at work
think of you more as a teddy bear than a
tiger? Do you whack off in your minivan
while listening to teen pop? You know
you'll be dead soon. You've missed out on
so much. It's not too late to make a
change. At the Midlife Crisis Center, we
know you've made a success of yourself.
Why are you sharing it with others? Why
not enjoy it while you have a chance?
What's holding you back? Cowardice? We'll
get you to the other side of your
despair. We specialize in real estate,
divorce attorneys, mistress placement,
plastic surgery, hair coloring and
replacement, male fur coats and much more.
With a designer clothing store and
sports car dealership on site, the
Midlife Crisis Center will help you
discover life while you still can.
Come with your wife, leave with a sports
car. While you've made a success of
yourself, her chest has gone south. How
can you have that trollop on your arm
for a second longer? The answer is: you
can't. Ignore your children, take yourself
seriously. Visit the Midlife Crisis
Center today. It's a favorite show with
serial killers and stalkers. Lonely
Hearts is...
Next, enter the sultry anonymity of night
and some of the day. You're on Lonely
Hearts on WCTR, West Coast Talk Radio, or,
as I like to call it, "We Can't Talk Right".
I love you all. I'm your host, Christy
MacIntyre. Let's go to the phones. Hi.
Christy, my wives and I love your show.
It's really helped. Ah, thanks! Do you want
to tell us about it? Uh,
no. Okay. Jenny on the line from Santa
Maria. Hi, Jenny. How's your heart? Broken,
like my arm and two of my ribs. What
happened? I married my childhood
sweetheart, but it all went wrong. He's
become a drunk, and he has a substance
problem, too, and now he beats me every
day. Stay with him, honey. After all, you're
only lonely when you're alone. But he
keeps threatening to kill me! Jenny, do
you know the meaning of the phrase "home
wrecker"? No. What about "selfish bitch"? I
want to bring people together, not break
them apart. Who's on the phones? It's a
big, lonely state out there. Christy, I'm
watching you right now in the shower.
Notice how many lonely hearts are
lunatics? You wonder why. Or perhaps not.
Brian from Las Venturas. Hey, dude, my
name's Brian. I'm calling from Las
Venturas. I want to talk about my heart.
Why do men just repeat back what you say
and never listen? Are you brain-dead,
Brian? Oh, actually, it's ironic that you
say that, 'cause my wife's been brain-
dead for years now. Oh, so sorry. I seemed
all insensitive for a second there,
possibly ruining my career. Would it help
if I slept with you? Probably not. Do it,
though, she wouldn't even notice. I mean, I
get away with it all the time now, even
after I did it with her sister. Actually,
our relationship is better than ever. The
passion is amazing. It's like I'm a new
person each time. If she was back to the
way she was before the accident, wow, I'd
put her in a coma myself! I mean, it's
fantastic. That's very informative. You
know, last night I wondered what it would
be like to be brain-dead. Then I watched
my five uncles. God, I'd love to live in
At Lonely Hearts, remember: a heart can mend, but
a divorce lasts forever, unless he makes
you a widow. Hello? Yeah, hello, Lonely Hearts.
Uh, I was just calling up there 'cause I was
listening, and I figured out, you know,
that I can help out some of y'all's
clients, you know. This is none other than
Jizzy, the proprietor of The Pleasure
Domes Club. If anybody is out there
lonely, first of all, with all the people
on this planet walking around, it's no
reason for anybody to be lonely, you
understand? That's why I'm in the
business of keeping people with company,
you know what I'm saying? People who got
low self-esteem and they need a pick-me-
up, they need to come down to The
Pleasure Domes, hang out with me, Jizzy,
and my girls, you know what I'm saying?
They going to keep you company, have you
feeling good. And this goes for everybody:
I don't care who you are, how old you are,
so come on down and hang out with me if
you're lonely, and I'm going to tell you
something: you won't be lonely from the
moment you walk in the door, 'cause
somebody's going to grab your hand and
it's going to be all about the get-down
from that. Good grief, that's not the way
Lonely Hearts works at all! Is anyone here
suffering? I want pain, misery, desolation,
all the important things. Hi, this is
Tamara. I'm a stalker. Ah, that's really
beautiful. Tell everyone about it, my man.
Well, I call him that even though he's
broken off all contact and is married to
someone else. I killed a gazelle and sent
its heart to him in an envelope. He liked
it so much, he told the police and even
the newspapers. Then I burnt down his
place of business, and now I have a
special surprise for him. You have a
great week! Isn't that really beautiful?
That's all we have time for. If your
heart is lonely, listen to other losers
and you won't be lonely anymore. You'll
want to spend the rest of your life in
isolation away from people, which is
progress, after all. Until next time, I
hope you enjoyed Lonely Hearts. It's
always fun to laugh at other people's
misery isn't it deal with your ignorance
in one minute flat complex issues in 60
seconds
wct let's be honest about things for a
second really honest you came out to the
West Coast to get away from something
everyone does let's face it the Midwest
is full of retards that's why we've got
the fastest growing population a massive
economy and absolutely no history or
culture you used to be a dork but you
moved here and suddenly you're cool San
Andreas is a land where you can be who
you want to be change your name come out
lie about your age form your own
religion call yourself an actor at
weight tables it just doesn't matter out
here everybody's at it until the awful
moment old friends or family come to
visit Janice understands maybe it's time
to change your identity don't let bad
memories blow your cover we'll teach you
all the things you need to alienate your
family quick they'll never think of
visiting you again select from a list of
weird religions that involve burning
things singing children's songs
backwards and loads of Television
worship we'll select a member of another
race or life form for you to claim as
your soulmate and your dietary habits
will go Pacific too people come to San
Andreas to escape their past we'll help
you lose contact with friends and family
fast Janice it's time to invent the new
you the news and all the other things
that really matter to you like
sensationalist
[ __ ] sexual realignment used to
require expensive of surgery months of
hormone treatments years of therapy and
you still ended up looking like a drag
queen now you can let the woman Inside
come out in the privacy and comfort of
your own home and it's as fast as this
slice see now I'm a woman thanks to
rapidy this do-it-yourself sexual
realignment kit includes everything you
need to go from Brad to Brenda in a gif
it's just snip chop stuff and swallow
and Away you go do it in the bathroom
and surprise your family with a new you
comes with with an instructional video
Rusty knife and tourniquet two aspirins
and 47 lb of estrogen it's all you need
when it's time for a change you want it
fast rapidit the do-it-yourself sexual
realignment kit be exactly who you want
to
be if you love to hear liberals wine and
conservatives lecture then stay tuned
for I say you say the future of America
threatened again this time we mean it
I'm Dr Phillips and I'm also Dr Phillips
today on the show decave paintings in
museum make us violent the anti- beef
movement both Hitler and musolini were
vegetarians and we take on the highly
charged debate about test two babies and
actually talk to one I have flashbacks
and go to hysterics and science class do
you know what it's like growing up in a
beaker that's all today on I say
us we share last names but that's about
it I'm pton that's my wife Mary and this
is I say you say where left is right and
right is wrong or East Meets West and
the West always wins that wall came down
darling yes unfortunately it did I I
don't know if you saw today's news so
who is in the right in this great
dialectical disaster is it as I think a
case of share and share alike love your
fellow man and all wear matching
jumpsuits while working on a collective
hydroponic Farm growing potatoes or kill
or be killed crush the weak and starve
the poor as my wonderful wife thinks you
decide or let us decide for you give us
a call and let my wife a professor in
Social Darwin ISM or me a lecturer in
pointless anthropology work things out
that's the problem with liberals they
don't know when to shut up and enjoy
Freedom let's go to the phones uh yeah
Hi here's the deal I'm really funny but
nobody wants to hire somebody funny I I
mean how is that fair I I mean I'm white
middle class very aidite um you know
Whatever that means. But people just
respond badly to me. I- I don't understand
it. Are you related to my
husband? Uh, I don't think so. I hope not.
Have you got a question about politics?
Yeah, sure. I know a lot about politics.
Hey, can I do your job? You know, I used to
be on the radio back in the day. Even my
husband can't do his job, you strange,
pathetic little sap. Let's have a real
caller, please. Hi, my name is Michelle. I'm
a first-time caller to the show. I wanted
to know what you guys thought about the
proposition to ban smoking. Well, this is
a simple issue. Smoking, democracy at work
again in our state. Seems like a good
thing when you first look at it, but
democracy only works when you agree with
it. Then it's best to favor a
totalitarian state. I'm not sure about
this one. I think smoking is an invasion
of my body, and I've always wanted to
shoot people. I'm right behind the
proposition. Me too. Thanks, Michelle. I
also wanted to say hi to my stepbrother,
Phil, who's been undergoing a hair
transplant today. Hey, Phil, if you're
listening, I hope it sticks this time. I
won't tell anyone you've got plugs, honey.
I'm really proud of you. That's great,
honey, but if you want shout-outs, call
the rap station. That's offensive, and I'm
really offended by what you're saying.
I'm a smoker. This used to be a free
country. When- Good point, Daryl. God, you're
good. Yes, good point. But remember, our
founding fathers grew tobacco. It relaxed
them between stressful stints of
genocide and witch-burning. And you're so
against raising taxes. Smokers pay more
taxes than anyone. My grandfather smoked
his whole life, and he lived until he was
32. So what I'm saying is, why can't we
encourage more smoking and use the money
to pay for better healthcare and some
cultural programs bringing expressive
dance and Sun worship back to the inner
cities? Worrying about the inner city has
ruined your academic career, and this
woolly thinking is going to ruin your
chances of getting anywhere with me
tonight promise the thing is smoking is
good because it lets people make a lot
of money but so is selectively culling
the population so what I'm proposing is
a change in the proposition let people
smoke but make cigarettes much cheaper
and force everyone to smoke that way we
weed out the week make a lot of money
and tax and keep our National Heritage
intact line two you're on I say you say
ha I listen every time to your show it
really made me think about the world the
whole new way I moved out of the city
cuz it sucks now I live in a compound
surrounded by barb wire and shoot and
kill anyone I don't recognize all my
land just want to say thank you that's
some quality broadcasting yeah thanks
that makes me feel a lot better about
myself have you got a question yeah I
got corpses from 15 illegal immigrants
in my yard I killed them all myself with
my bare hands can I get a tax break for
all this unpaid work good good question
I would certainly hope so ask your
accountant if you can register them as
dependents then hide most of your net
worth offshore at a complex money
laundering system designed to support
the drugs trade then you can pay
virtually no taxes and complain about
how awful you think the whole country is
knowing you're doing as little as
possible to help cool thanks that's good
advice I'm appalled at you Mary Phillips
why because that man has a garden full
of corpses and you're talking about
money laundering yes it's a great
opportunity for some profit Centric
thinking you missed a wonderful
opportunity to talk about Recycling and
organ donation oh God give me strength I
married a fool I married a fo you know
when we first met Payton I thought you
were So Glamorous with your long hair
and big Ideas you were studying for a
PhD in cultural ceramic history or cross
cultural underwear or something and I
was very young very foolish now I see
...you for what you are." "And what's that?"
"Exactly: an intellectual cesspit, a
middle-class disaster, a guilt trip
wrapped in neurosis, and completely
unable to function in this society! No
wonder I've begun to sleep around." "And on
that note, we have to go visit our
marriage therapist, who is a conniving
[ __ ] and won't write me any more
prescriptions for painkillers." "Remember:
when the left wing and the right wing
come together, the country can really get
going straight off a cliff!" We'll see you
next
time! Boy, I can't imagine what those guys
are like in the bedroom, but I'm sure
it's a bit like the Bay of Pigs. That was
I Say, You Say. At home, at work, or in
rehab, listen to
WCTR. Next up, we've got the news! This time,
some of it's true! Who are we
kidding? I'm Leanne for WCTR News. Here's
everything that matters in simple terms
so you can understand: a dire warning
from America's gun manufacturers, "Learn
yourself or die," and the Louisiana
Purchase: B for women? Plus, wallpaper!
Something big is happening in home
furnishings, don't be left behind! Our top
story: Alan Crawford, manager of the
rapper Madd Dogg, murdered. Madd Dogg recently
launched a clothing label and compared
himself favorably to Jesus and Gandhi
while sniffing a lot. The brutal murder
remains unsolved. Police suspect foul
play. Richard Burns is at the scene. Uh, no,
actually, Leanne, that story wasn't very
interesting, so I rode with San Fierro
police detective Turk Martin, who is
assigned to curtail illegal street
racing activities in the countryside
surrounding Los Santos and San Fierro. You
know what's really cool? You get to chase
these slimeballs really fast, and if you
hit someone, wow, it's never your fault! Oh,
this is so cool, you get to eat while you
work! Let me see that. Hey, stop now,
[ __ ], or we'll shoot out your tires!
Put that down! Ah, dude, don't be a dick!
Let me shoot out his tires, I'm doing,
like, 110 mph right now!
Okay. In foreign news, a heavily
discredited former dictator in Latin
America is claiming a U.S. government
agency sold him weapons in exchange for
drugs that are now being sold on the
streets of our cities. Government
officials strongly deny the claim. "Why
would we do something so crazy? We don't
need drugs, we have good hookups already!
Besides which, do you know how much
cocaine is needed to buy a helicopter?
It's more than I can snort!" Leanne for WCTR
News. Stay worried out there.
Come live the
mystery...
...at Glory Hole Theme Park! Cool off in our water sports park.
"I'll show your kids a great time!" It's
something they'll never forget and talk
about for years to come—especially at
therapy sessions. It's the place for
magic and
adventure, leaving me free to shop and
get lipo! "Who's ready for the incredible
Dribbles' Voyage?" "Sherry, can we come too?"
"This is a journey you must undertake
alone. It can be dark and scary." She'll shriek
with de-
-light! "What's that hole in the wall for?" "You wait
and see, you'll be amazed!" [ __ ] the
suit! Glory Hole Theme Park, open every
day till 3:00 a.m.! "Today we marched on
from Fort Strother after sunrise to a
Creek village where our troops fought
the savages and shot them like dogs!"
"Honey, it's time for bed." "Hang on a second,
I'm killing a squaw! Take that, you pagan
[ __ ]!" Oh no, him and his Commemorative
Miniatures. "My husband was getting so
bored at work, and he didn't have an
interest to spend money on, but he's
always loved history. Then I heard about
grown men who like to play with toy
soldiers." War is so interesting with
Commemorative Miniatures! "I began by
faithfully rebuilding The Charge of the
Light Brigade, and after that, the Trail
of Tears. I've built accurate recreations
of 15 significant battles, as well as
training camps, prisoner-of-war camps, and
forced-labor death camps. Now I spend all
my time painting toy soldiers and
attending conventions." Commemorative
Miniatures: they're instantly collectible
and a great value. For just 37 monthly
payments of $19.99, you get a starter pack
allowing you to recreate the battle of
your choice. Show your inability to deal
with present-day problems by
recreating scenes of mass slaughter from
the past! "Reenacting battles is great for
your marriage, too. One night my husband's
General Custer, the next Napoleon. On
Saturdays, I'm a Cambodian villager
and he's a G.I. that has his way with me."
"Then I kill her." Commemorative Miniatures:
they're not toys, they're very valuable,
collectible, two-inch model armies. This is
a hobby you can't afford to miss out on!
If you're into exploring exotic places
and forbidden fruit, stay tuned. It's The
Wild Traveler next. Support for The Wild
Traveler is brought to you by the
Ultimate Disc-in-the-Dark Association
of America, who encourages you to get out
hard.
Hello, I'm James Pedeaston, world
traveler, and this is The Wild Traveler.
We're discussing the world and all of
its many pleasures. Let me put it like
this: why have a hot dog from an uncaring
vendor by the bathroom when you can
attend a beer-guzzling marathon in
Germany with enormous men and taste a
wonderful German's bock? The world is full
of
incredible things, and you can discover
them for yourself. Come along, I'll take
you there.
It was dusk, and the sun bled red over
the city in Thailand as Chen brought me
a sparkling water—a delicate, handsome,
lovely young boy. The world of
possibilities! But war is folly, and we
can only unite by visiting these epochs
of culture where a man can be himself:
smoke cigarettes, dress in gladiator
clothing if he likes. We mustn't force
our way and culture upon other peoples;
rather, breathe it in, become part of it.
Maybe Hemingway was right about love,
maybe Freud was. We're all fighting
inside to let a wild creature mate in
the rain. "I travel, therefore I am." This is
a show that embraces culture from around
the world. Let's take our first caller.
"Hello?" "Yeah, I totally agree with you
about Australia, and you're right, the
Moon is [ __ ]. Also, I was thinking of
visiting Colombia. Do you have any
recommendations?" "Oh, there's fantastic forms of
recreation to be had in Colombia! It's a
blizzard of excitement, and cheap! The
rails are great and long. Bolivia is not
bad either, or Peru. You'll be surprised
to find out how the party never stops."
"How's the food?" "Well, a lighter is the
most you need to cook up food, but
there's scarcely time to eat, my boy!
You'll meet fascinating people, feel so
comfortable you'll rip your clothes off
and
howl for days! Next caller." "Yeah, hi, my—my
name is Geraldine, calling from Carcer City.
This is such a great country, why would
you go anywhere else? It's unpatriotic to
travel! I mean, I got war, famine,
depression, and pollution right here on
my doorstep! And parents, don't let kids
Interrail after college! They'll come
back with ludicrous misconceptions about
healthcare, charity, and civilization!
Europe is not the real world. This is!"
"Well, I love to slum about in a dirty
youth hostel with communal showers as
much as the next man—sometimes more—but
I have to agree, Europe is overrated.
Eastern Europe was good for a few years
after the Wall came down, but even there,
the police are too strict. You just can't
let your hair down! There are far more
unexplored pleasures to be had in the
Far East. Next caller, you're on The Wild
Traveler." "Hey, I've been listening to you
go on and on about traveling. Do you know
how expensive it is to fly to Asia?
Russia saw the light; they're all coming
here to set up crime families and run
numbers! South America? Everyone went
extinct there! They have less culture
there than the content of my toilet bowl.
Rainforest, schmainforest! In Mexico, if I
wanted to be that close to my ancient
ancestors, I'd be banging my
mother-in-law instead of my wife's best
friend!" "Look, we can fight like beasts or
agree to disagree. I'm sure the summit of
your aspirations in life is a
cheerleader with fake cans, but some of
us think a little more exotically than
this. Next caller. ¡Vamos! ¡Buenos días y
noches! 'If you don't smile, I won't deep
hard...' Sorry, got lost for a second. Speak."
"Hey, I love this show, I'm a huge fan. I
visit all the places you've recommended,
and in a lot of them, they're still
talking about you. I even saw posters of
you in the customs booth at the airport
in the Philippines. You rock."
"Ah, no doubt. I loved Manila, had a great time." "But that
show you did last week... What was the name
of that spiritual center in Bangkok?"
"The Wild Dragon Happy Ending. Very spiritual.
You will find inner peace."
"Awesome, I can't wait. Thanks, man."
"Yes, we all love to travel, get away from it all, get away
from the people with computers and their
databases, the police harassing you for
doing nothing. I just hate showing up to
someplace to enjoy myself, and people are
being forced from their homes by war or
famine or whatever. Life is great, stop
ruining it. Next caller."
"Hey, the FBI wants to talk to me about a perfectly innocent
collection of vacation photographs
overseas that I had no idea were being
taken! I mean, any ignorant fool can
misinterpret... I-I was teaching them how
to swim! I have a lot of experience with
this." "I want you to stop for a moment and
let me read from my travel journal. I
think everyone should keep a journal:
paste pictures, notes... Sometimes people
object to you taking their picture, but a
few pennies of their local currency and
they will fawn over you. Some people think
this is patronizing, but I think it is
fair enough. They need the money, and I
need the company. Besides which, it is the
oldest profession."
What? Oh, time for me to head south again!
I'm James Pedeaston, and this has been The
Wild
Traveler. This is WCTR, committed to
bringing you shows like The Wild
Traveler, the show that takes you around
the world and abandons you at the
airport. If you crave news,
WCTR: West Coast Talk Radio! Next up, it's
sensationalist propaganda—I mean, the
news.
I'm Leanne for WCTR News. Here's what you
should think matters. Breaking news:
strange lights spotted over the desert!
Here's an eyewitness report: "I seen some
strange lights over the
desert. Yep, sure did." Currently, we have no
more information. In other news, residents
are upset at taxes funding the Los
Santos Museum of Natural History. "This
fascination with the past is ridiculous!
I mean, I've been to Pangaea, it was
disgusting, and our ancestors were idiots!
My grandmother can barely talk, she's so
stupid!" Also, organ theft: how to know if
you're going to wake up in a bathtub of
ice. More gang violence: we go to the
streets of Los Santos with Richard Burns.
"That's right, Leanne. I'm Richard Burns,
and I am in a terrible part of town—a
town under siege by hoodlums. Gang and
drug wars are plaguing the city." "Hey, you
want this part or what?" "Yeah, just put it
in the van." "A huge, sudden upsurge in
cocaine sales has been reported. The
street wars between gangs of Ballas and
Grove Street hoodlums came to a head
recently, when several senior Grove
Street gang members were killed, while
others were incarcerated. The police
describe that as, and I'm quoting,
'excellent news.' Back to you, Leanne." "Hey,
has this been cut?" "Hell no, it's good [ __ ]!"
Bridges linking Red County and Flint
County finally reopened recently, after
long delays following the earthquake. The
Governor congratulated himself
extensively. In entertainment news, first
it was The Budgies, then it was Love Fist,
now the British Invasion starts up again...
this time from the Scottish Village of
madchester new band The gning Chimps are
tipped for stardom we caught up with the
lead singer Macker when he landed in Los
Santos airport the ging chimps are
coming to America man we're going to
take over M my words and wipe my [ __ ]
ass lock up your daughters and get the
drugs in Manchester's in the area lean
for wct news keep it locked on it's
getting worse out
there the news and all the other things
that really matter to you like
sensationalist
[ __ ] coming up next it's time for
the man who can grow anything big and
strong it's gardening with Maurice
broadcasting live from his
garden howdy Doodles this is gardening
with Maurice and I am Maurice ever since
man was kicked out of the garden he's
been striving to get back in I believe
all of life's answers can be found in
something as simple as a flower it's
stamman it's pistol it's pollin just
like me and you we're going to the
phones hello you're on gardening with
Maurice I am Maurice go ahead caller uh
yes thanks for having me on I'm a big
fan uh I have a question my melons
aren't big enough I thought they were
going to keep growing but they just
stopped my next door neighbor has huge
melons and everyone just spawns over
them oh they taste so sweet oh look how
firm they are what do I do oo I would
love to see your melons look gardening
is a spiritual light Journey where you
become one with nature however sometimes
nature needs some chemicals to you know
kind of kick things into action there's
a fantastic fertilizer I use called
piteri it needs to be injected with a
needle so be very very careful and
inject that right into your melons and
they will grow enormous thanks so much
Maurice you're the best yes I know I
know that I've been at one with nature
for so long now I can't remember what
it's like to sleep inside next caller
God I was on hold forever uh I've heard
that facials are great really make you
look younger oh yes listen honey I
should know when you look like a train
wreck you need a little makeup or some
such you sound like a lonely spinster
with two [ __ ] cats it's the menopause
Maurice I'm having hot flashes okay
taking a pause from men huh you know I
should try that for your face try
Nature's cosmetic camouflage Cleopatra
took milk baths with cereal each morning
try Tomatoes too the acid is great it
makes your face just peel right off hey
thanks Maurice that's me fertilizing
Minds enough of you voyers out there and
your vicarious gardening I want you to
join in on the fun when you stick your
hands in the mystery of Nature and you
pull out a worm or a tuber God I love
tubers so plump and juicy hello Mike
from prickle Pine in Los venturus hey
Maurice first time caller my name is
Mike I work on my lawn and garden all
weekend long cuz I got this raging edus
complex and I like drinking beer and
riding around on the lawnmower too
because you know the vibrations are kind
of cool but what really killing me is I
can't seem to get these weeds out of the
driveway I tried Napal I tried gasoline
of course okay stop stop stop stop stop
st listen I want you to listen to me are
you listening to me Mark it's Mike okay
good that was a test okay I know what
your name is I know it's Mark now listen
up listen closely I want you to pave
over your entire yard okay I want you to
just pave it over with cement or
asphalt or whatever listen I have the
Maurice Mansion completely covered in
AstroTurf inside and outside which by
the way is particularly handy when some
big football players come over and we
have a little midnight match of ultimate
disc in the yard now when your lawn is
beautiful and green all year long you
can focus on the important matters if
you get my drift you see gardening with
Maurice is sponsored by the happy farmer
Yahoo if you're afraid someone will
steal your Tomatoes why not grow
tomatoes in your closet indoors like me
the happy farmer Hydroponics and more
next story to blos I'm Maurice until
next time dig a hole and plant
yourself that was the show that
generates more phone calls than any
other on wct gardening with Maurice the
news and all the other things that
really matter to you like people dying
lady on fire bodies everywhere and
explosions is hanging from the trees
this accident is really cool wct
need to meet someone very special Lonely
Hearts is next welcome to Lonely Hearts
the place where we make dreams come true
where we bring people together and we
remind you about what really matters in
matters of the heart great abs and a fat
wallet hi lonely hearts on the phone
speak hello my name is zero I'm a
first-time caller and uh uh to the show
I've used the telephone before but I am
having real trouble with women I I don't
know
any yes I don't know any well we all go
through lean spells you know after a
drought you'll sell for anything that
drops out of the sky especially illegal
immigrants stowed away in the landing
gear so exotic no no no I I do I I
masturbate quite often if that's what
you're implying I'm I'm just saying uh
this is quite a lean spell lady well
that's too bad still after winter comes
spring and after the rain the trees
blossom and drop leaves and [ __ ] all
over my yard well this is quite to
Winter do you understand what I'm saying
try try a nuclear winter I've never even
been near a woman close enough to gra I
don't know what to say well that's odd
considering you give advice I don't
think I can help look I'm just being
honest here I wouldn't even subject you
to a hooker please lady I don't want to
be celibate there's a lot of people out
there with a vow of celibacy and look at
all the joy they bring to the world I'd
love to help but it sounds serious and I
like to keep things strictly trivial
who's on the phone how's your heart I
saw documentary about this serial killer
and fell in love with him he's been
turned down for parau for eating a guard
oh my poor baby and I can't get a
conical visit that's so terrifying
Maniac love doesn't have to be a crime
like when you would write your name over
and over maniacally on a spiralbound
notebook in class just wishing he'd turn
around during algebra class and say do
you want to study tonight and then he's
so overwhelmed with passion when he sees
your pooms and then you hello am I on
heart um yes you are oh I couldn't tell
I was on hold forever and I heard some
pathetic woman weeping about her high
school algebra fantasy don't you
remember how unexperienced you were in
high school it was over in 3 seconds I
could never hold my own oh yeah maybe
for you do you have a question I just
can't meet the right person I want to
meet someone special I'll get off the
phone who's that your sister no that's
just my wife look I need to meet someone
really special ideally once a week in a
motel wearing leather speaking Germann
um that's great next caller hello jez
remember me I am Fernando martinz oh God
not you again look it was a mistake we
all get drunk at
funerals okay the heart can only takes
so much until it explodes or gets
clogged with tar from postp Passion
redwoods talk to you soon remember if
you're going to smoke in bed love is
like an ashtray butts one after another
you feel like [ __ ] afterwards and you
wake up with someone else's lighter
we'll see you next time on Lonely Hearts
no wonder these people are alone that
was lonely hearts opinions are free
which is why we're here it's news and
talk that our sponsors agree on
wct let's go find out what's really
happening in the world
news I'm Leanne for wct news we distort
you can't rort breaking news is
skateboarding turning your son gay also
San Fiero has been hit by one10 scale
chaos recently following a series of
many terrorist attacks tiny techn
terrorists are suspected more on that
story as it comes in a district attorney
is facing a long jail sentence after he
was arrested outside the vanol hotel
trying to escape with well over a ton of
marijuana police are currently
investigating claims it was for personal
use staying with pot police are
celebrating the destruction of a major
Hall of marijuana in Flint County
recently unfortunately the huge fire
caused problems for local Wildlife much
of which was found eating chocolate
listening to the same band over and over
and buying fractal artwork Richard Burns
is on the scene oh man I am wicked bab
hey man in the movie you got shot but
you look great baby hey who's the guy
with the antl oh [ __ ] no dude dude I was
just checking to see if she was in heat
no it's it's cool dude she's your do
dude be
cool all right inhabitants of bone
County reported further inexplicable
lights over the desert yeah sure did
government officials blame the water
supply and more positive news came from
Street good guy Big Smoke who today
unveiled his new orphanage in a ceremony
in Los Santos yes thank you thank you
I'd just like to say this is a great day
for the impoverished and disadvantage of
Los Santos and it's a real honor that I
am as generous as I am I remember when I
was a little boy my dear mother would
ask me what I wanted to be when I grew
up and I said Mom I want to be a savior
it's a great opportunity the Big Smoke
orphanage teaches kids important skills
I was an orphan I struggled I saw
friends make mistakes and get pulled
from the path of righteousness but now
thanks to the generosity of a great man
like me kids is going to be saved Big
Smoke baby remember the name in crime
news Asian gang trouble in San Fiero is
on the rise with problems developing
between Chinese Triad gangs and
Vietnamese gangs a government official
released this statement hey if they want
to kill each other let them it's great
it means your taxes go down I'm Leanne
for wct news stay
indoors you're good but let's be honest
you're not perfect and that's not
American we strive to be number one in
everything Sports politics economics
homelessness degeneracy Los Santos is
the home of beauty and glamour for the
whole world live up to society's
expectations Play Your Part your body is
a work of art don't leave it half
finished it's time for your creative
plastic surgery will'll make your face
as tight as a drum we'll suck fat out of
your body with an industrial pump
increase your confidence with fake
breasts to ensure people know what
you're all about for the more
adventurous why to try an extra nose or
three breasts you know how much men like
breasts can you imagine how Wild they'll
go for others my wife was complaining
that she did all the work carried the
baby for 9 months had painful labor it's
not fair to her my nipples are useless
that's why I Had Creative plastic
surgery I got a set of UDS installed now
my son can suck my UTS while I'm
watching the game the fellas at the bar
love them too men never stared
lasciviously at my ass then I had a tail
attached now people can't stop looking
Beauty Is Not skin deep it's less than
that creative plastic surgery achieve
your own
Utopia this is wct committed to bringing
you shows like the wild traveler even if
we received a ceent assist talk is cheap
especially on this station featuring
more Rich angry people complaining
wct cocka dooodle do it's time for
chicken COA dooodle do is time for a
feast eat a 90 piece bucket you can
tell he's toing Bell the chicken is a
Bird with a tin brain so we assume he
doesn't feel any pain. We shrink their
heads and we breed them fast: six wings,
40 breasts, then gas. Cock-a-doodle-doo,
psychotic, crazy cock-a-doodle-doo! Factory
farming insane, we denied it all before
our stock price fell. Come down to Clucking
Bell! Clucking Bell, if you enjoy it, the
chicken didn't die in vain.
The most boring show with a brand new host:
Entertaining America with
Lazlow! Welcome to Entertaining America, this
is Lazlow. I got to say it, pardon me, but uh,
don't call it a comeback, I've been here
for years, just unemployed. But I'm back,
running the media. Got to love this West
Coast vibe, everybody here is so
laid-back and lazy. I'm here with a man
who gets paid to talk for a living, it's
incredible, what a concept. Um, he's called
a rapper, OG Loc. How are you, OG Loc?
It's OG Loc! OG Loc, you hear me, player? Yes, of
course I hear you, you're only a few feet
away, man. Listen, I'm a big fan. I—I love
rap. I—I think, I mean, singing songs about
yourself, that's awesome.
H-H-How you living? Straight. Really? Are
you really straight? What, you going to
question me? Dude, it's cool. If somebody
passes it to me, I don't ask questions.
It's probably not laced anyway. So who
out there wants to talk to OG Loc? Caller,
you're on Entertaining America. I love
the way you rap about the Louisiana
Purchase. Straight. You know, the French
sold us Louisiana so we would have a
place to show our tits. My point exactly!
Yeah, we need more naked Liberty. Exactly.
Look, I'm no rapper, even though I dress
like one, but I think I could really get
into, you know, getting hammered, singing
about setting things on fire, shooting up
funerals, you know, striking poses, smoking
a lid. Exactly. You see, the Constitution
was written on reefer by dudes with
wooden teeth. You see, my clothing
company, Loc-Down, home of the G, says this:
"I love reefer." It's the rules if you're a
rapper. Wow, those sound like some great
rules. You know, you get a lot of flak in
the media these days. At a recent press
conference, your manager came to your
defense: "A lot of people say gangster rap
is misogynistic posturing by fake-ass
idiots who spend more time in drama
school than they ever did pimping or
hustling dope. Well, I assure you OG Loc
is the real thing. He's hated women all
his life, he sold drugs to school
children, he's murdered innocent people
just for kicks, but he rhymes like an
angel, and I assure you it's all in a
good cause. So either way, you can feel
good about yourself listening to this
music." Well, that was very informative. Big
Smoke is doing a lot for the community,
or... or to it. He sounds like a great guy.
So I want to get in on this rap thing. Do
I have to breakdance, you know, do the
windmill? Hey, can you body pop? Come on,
Lazlow, you know OG ain't no playboy, I ain't
down with that shit, it ain't gangsta! I
walk the walk, you know what I'm saying?
Fresh! Yo, I'm... I'm down, I'm into walking,
too, but I was thinking maybe we could
have a break-off, you know? I get spin on
my back... You being funny? I'm trying to be...
Watch it, fool, I warn you! I got the
streets, I got a rep! Me and my man Smoke,
we took over! I've been gangbanging
since I was three! Ice-cold killer! Excuse
me, gangbanging? I never understood that.
I mean, other guys in the room... Like I'm
ice cold, shit, don't make me dump on you,
G! I'm the streets, man! I am danger! I'm
taking rap in a whole new direction! From
now on, it's about making words rhyme! And
I'm going toe-to-toe with you in a
minute! Why do you rappers get so worked
up? You're rich, you've won, stop shooting
at each other, you know? And you keep
saying, "I'm from the streets." Well, you
know what, dude? Everyone has a street in
front of their house, that doesn't make
you cool. Oh, we got a comedian, huh? You
got scratched, huh? Fuck you! Damn you,
mock-ass bitch-punk trick-buster fool! I
don't... I don't know what you said, but uh,
hey, this ought to calm you down. I brought
you some malt liquor. You a buster fool!
Lucky I don't hang you out the window
or turn you out, 'cause I'm also a pimp,
including dudes! I'll pimp anything, you
hear me? No, dude, I hear you loud and
clear, man. You will pimp anything. Listen,
how many hot women need a man? 'Cause I mean,
it's kind of been a dream of mine to
sleep with housewives. Are you dissing my
hoes? Shit, no no no no, dude, uh,
your hoes are shit, your hoes are shit! You a
buster! What are you? I'm a buster. I'm a
buster, what—whatever that is, dude. Put...
put the gun away. Don't diss my strap! I
love your strap, you're a great gun. Look,
I'm... I'm just coming down off the '80s,
please don't shoot me, homie! Relax, fool,
no one's getting dumped on. I'm a warrior
poet, I tell a cautionary tale about
life on the streets. You know only too
well, that was OG Loc. Hey man, it's been a
real pleasure. Straight. Yeah, good luck
with the music, hope you can make a
killing. We'll see you next time. Maybe
I'll get to take some callers like I want to,
if WCTR wasn't holding me back, man. This
has been Entertaining America with Lazlow.
Peace and chicken grease. So that's how
you're going to be entertained. The news
and all the other things that really
matter to you, like sensationalist
shit. Tired of all the sunshine and
good weather? Looking for a real American
vacation? Visit the shining jewel in the
Rust Belt crown, Carcer City! It's a real
man's vacation. The pride of a nation is
in Carcer City. It's steel, ice, and poverty.
Spend a romantic evening in the beauty
of the nighttime river glow at the
Flaming River. Watch real men who make
things lose their jobs and fight on our
special "Closing the Mill" guided tour.
Come see what we're really made of. This
is real America: drunk, proud, unemployed,
and angry. Hear the eagle roar in Carcer
City! This is what the Heartland is all
about. Is the world ending? We hope so, we
need the ratings. The news is
next. Lianne for WCTR News. News with
the bottom line in mind. Top news stories: Was
Moses really from Ohio? Chairs, the silent
killer in your home? Now WCTR Traffic and
Transit. After months, all bridges have
been reopened. Bone County, Tierra Robada,
and Las Venturas County are now linked up
with the rest of the state. Locals
celebrated by mass outbreaks of
xenophobia and inbreeding. Also, police
are celebrating the removal of a major
crack cocaine ring by undercover police
that has virtually stopped the flow of
drugs into Los Santos. Richard spoke to a
man on the scene. "That's right, Lianne,
it's another victory for prohibition!
Police are really celebrating after this
one. One officer told me his amazing true-
life story of how he infiltrated a drug
ring and how cool it was to get paid to
get high." "Yeah, I was undercover smoking
crack every day, you know, just to be one
of them. I even took my wife undercover
and made her a crack whore! Say hello to
the newsman, whore!" "Hey, don't I know you?
The Rusty Trombone, right?" "I doubt it."
"Shit, you're—you're crazy!" Back to you,
Lianne. Police are struggling to solve
the mystery of a container ship found
deserted and full of bodies. The FBI is
investigating, and government officials
denied the existence of an area of Bone
County that isn't on the map. Someone who
was unprepared to be named said the
so-called place that isn't called
anything doesn't exist, and if it did,
we'd name it something. And where is Madd
Dogg? One-time record exec, the rapper has
battled alcoholism and egomania for many
years, and recently missed a concert in
Las Venturas. Staying in Venturas, it used
to be a patch of desert, then it was a
mob town, now it's the corporate
headquarters of America. Richard explains
from the streets. "That's right, Lianne, it
used to be a patch of desert, then it was
a mob town, now it is the corporate
headquarters of America. Back to you in
the studio." In foreign news, we have war,
famine, pestilence, and a lot of envy
aimed at our way of life. Stay at home,
it's better that way. I'm Lianne Forget, WCTR
News. Stay alert, they're after us! This is
well-known philanthropist Big Smoke, and
you're listening to
WCTR. Make a difference to your community,
keep our cities drug-free. Look, I'm doing
my bit, how are you helping? At home, at
work, or in rehab, listen to
WCTR. Have you heard the number one
gardening show in San Andreas? If not,
here's what you're missing: pesticides,
exploring damp gopher holes, my new
walk-in closet. What's on your mind about
gardening? "Tubers and... and root vegetables."
"Oh God, not you again." "Is it okay to cut
the eyes out of a potato and eat it?" "Well,
why don't I come over and cut your eyes
out and eat you? What a silly question. If
you purchase the Gardening with Maurice
calendar, it's in the August section next
to the picture of the firefights and the
cute Pomeranian puppy." "Yeah, I bought that
calendar, but on every page you're naked
and in a different garden,
and the guys at work make fun of me!" "Well,
listen, if you're ashamed of your human
body, then keep your clothes on! I am
blossoming in those pictures, and I
wanted to capture it on film. But I
happen to be proud of my human body, as
much as I am proud of my flowers when
they are blossoming. I like to take
pictures of them; when I'm blossoming, I
like to take pictures of it!" Next caller.
"Hi, I live here in Bone County, and I
can't get nothing to grow. Have you had
any ch—"
"I sure do! I got seven kids, and some of
them's got the same daddy." "Well, look,
you've grown something: little miniature
idiots that look like you! Move out of
the desert, you bitch!" "I guess you're
right. Well, thanks, Maurice." "I am right, and
I'm Maurice on Gardening with Maurice."
Gardening with Maurice, only on
WCTR. Area 53 is next. Don't say we didn't
warn you! Did the government recruit
schoolchildren to beat you up in school?
Are goldfish really communist
spies? I'm Marvin Trill, this is Area 53. I'm
broadcasting live from my mobile home in
the desert. I am telling you, it's hot
like alien balls in here! Going to the
conspiracy lines. "Hi, my name's Adam. First,
I've been doing some much-needed
surveillance in the desert while
hang gliding. I've noticed a peculiar
trailer compound where a man is running
around in a spacesuit conducting weird
rituals with doormats." "What? Well, he
probably wants you to leave him alone.
Get a real hobby, like pretending to be
someone on TV." Next caller. "Hey, it's me
again." "You?" "Now, come on, man, tell the
people about the desert. How come there's
something missing, huh? A map with things
missing ain't a real map, and that's what
they feed us. That and female hormones
in the water supply!" "Yeah, I hear you on
that one." "Well, I'll call back when I got
proof." "You better not be tracing this
call!" "I don't trace calls. Everything in
life should be anonymous. I tell my
various partners that all the time." Rick
from Blueberry Acres, what do you think,
K-L-A-M? "I couldn't have said it better
myself. Crun truth is wisdom, brother, and
brother wisdom works! That's why we made
it up." You and I have a lot in common.
Vivian is calling in from Carcer City
and wants to talk about crop circles. "Oh
wow, I never thought I'd actually make it
on the show!" "Is that because you have a
girl's name? Well, here's a conspiracy:
your mom hates you!" "Holy shit, how'd you
know that?" Next caller. "My name is Neil. I
go to a lot of demonstrations to pick
up religious pamphlets. None of them say
anything about... about the aliens." "Try
reading between the lines, and if that
doesn't work, do some speed! Then you'll
understand all about the aliens, and just
where you were planted." Mike on line 10.
"Man, I think my dentist is attracted to
me. She knocks me unconscious and has her
way with me. And it's unlikely, but it
could be true. My teeth feel great, but I
feel icky, all dirty and used like a sex
object." "I'll tell you what makes me feel
icky: the fact I haven't washed in two
months. Whatever you do, trust nobody." Next
caller. "I am a doormat. My name is 6323..."
69439. Well, that's not a very original
name. I didn't know robots listen to this
show. "We know what you are doing to my
domestic beef, brothers and sister." Enough of
that. Little guy sounds like he's been
programmed for evil. All right, let's get
to the real meat and potatoes: newsmen
lying to our face about weather balloons,
historians ignoring my proof that WWII
didn't happen, the FDA infiltrated by the
very device they're supposed to regulate—
the plug-in mind control devices. But we'll
have to leave that for now. You are
leaving Area 53. You've been abducted.
Until next time, stay alert. They're after
you. You're leaving Area 53. Check your
rectum. The news and all the other things
that really matter to you, like people
dying, lady on fire, bodies everywhere, and
explosions hanging from the trees.
This accident is really cool!
[Music]
WCTR. Hello? Uh, hey, it's me, Jonathan. I... I
don't know a Jonathan. Yeah, that's the
name they gave me at the orphanage after
you put me up for adoption. How could you
give me away? Bring the family together
again: San Andreas Telephone, for those
difficult conversations. If you're into
exploring exotic places and forbidden
fruit, stay tuned. It's The Wild Traveler
next. Hello. Hello, I'm James Piston,
World Traveler, and this is The Wild Traveler.
From Peru to San Andreas in 8 days by
balloon. Often, while lounging around
garden parties, we forget the brave
workers worldwide who toil day and night
for the products we consume. Some are
even so dedicated to our happiness, they
carry products in balloons shoved inside
themselves. To be a balloon...
floating...
mesmerizing. We go to the phones. Yes, we
do. I can't believe you actually
recommended we go to Barbados on our
honeymoon! It was revolting! There were
poor people! I live in Vinewood to be
away from poor people! Barbados is lovely.
Look, I want to be very clear: I'm not
racist, just careful, okay? I like
all-inclusive resorts where you can drink
as much as you want, be around other
people from San Andreas, and the only
interaction you have with the locals is
if you need a cocktail or... or some spice
in the bedroom with your husband. Well, that
sounds lovely. With people like
you, it's no wonder we don't bother
curing cancer. Next caller, you're on The Wild
Traveler.
Yeah, it's funny you go on and
on about other countries, but you live
here. America rules, you commie! Eat me!
Well, we've been trying. Tom, you're on the
line. I'm so sick of England! "Oh, let's go
to the pub." They're all alcoholics! At
least we drink a 24-pack in private
instead of hanging in some social
setting making a fool of ourselves!
People say it's so civilized in Europe;
they got thousands of years of history.
Well, I saw a movie about Europe once and
I was disgusted! I mean, people still
defecate in their living rooms and cover
it up with dirt like a cat! You can't
find a decent turlet anywhere, or a good
chicken wing, and the strippers overcharge!
Good Lord, you Philistine! You should
stay out of England. I hear there is a
casino in Venturas that is just like
the rest of the world, only with better
toilets and full of morons like you. Do
you want culture, or do you want safety?
It's your choice. Personally, I want
irrigation of the colonic variety, but
that's a whole different story, and it is
early. Let's go to the phones. Who's on
the phones? No one? Come on, call up!
Anyone! It wouldn't be like this in Peru,
I can tell you. There, I once made a phone
call with 30 boys sitting on my lap—not
because I paid them; they wanted to be
there! Or in Mali, where nobody knows
what a phone is, and a lot of people have
never even heard of plastic surgery or
the [censored] theme park there. The glory
holes aren't theme parks, I can tell you!
It's violent and bloody and authentic!
What are you scared of, you wimps? Give me
a call! Someone, please! Hello, you're on
Wild Traveler. Where are you? I'm on a
cliff. How romantic! I want to jump. I know
what you mean—jump into the unknown. How
can it be a sin if it feels good? Anyway,
what's your question? Why am I here? I
don't know, why are you there? Where are
you, Kenya? No, I'm in Verdant Bluffs. Lonesome
place. I'd jump if I were you. I want to
go to Hell. Me too! Buy a refrigerator
magnet when you get there. On with the
show. Any callers?
No. Okay, maybe I should hit the travel
log again. This is from my diary in Sri
Lanka: "For a few rupees a day, I have
employed the services of a young man who
has been my guide and pleasure, as well
as travel. There is something very exotic
about him, Asinda. He could be a boy, but
like many locals, in certain lights he
looks just like a little girl. He is a
real minx who knows exactly what he is
doing to be..." Oh, wrong page. Here we are.
"Asinda took me deep into the jungle, and there
we took part in an ancient rite of
passage for adolescents on the cusp of
adulthood. We hunted each other in a game
very similar to the ancient games of
kiss-chase I used to play..." No, wrong
page. "Asinda has left me. I'm broken. I
thought I meant something, but it seems
he would rather become a fisherman than
follow me in an exotic life of
degeneracy and narcotics as my houseboy.
I hate myself. Why does this keep
happening to me?" Oh, wrong bit again.
Where's the page about watching the
elephants mate and it being really
disturbing and making me slightly
jealous of both parties? Hey, has someone
been stealing pages out of my journal? My
producer is jealous! He keeps stealing my
stuff and lending it to people. Just last
week, I heard him saying government
agents wanted to look at it. What a load
of trash. Ah, we have a call! Finally!
I just want to tell people about a great
holiday. You mean vacation! We call it
vacation! What is it? Searching for a yeti
in the Himalayas? Learning to play an
Alpine horn? Hunting for pythons in
Africa? Oh, Canada! But what about a young
man to peel grapes? What about fine local
herbs? Hey, it's cheap and it's plentiful.
Apart from the rent boys, what about the
food poisoning? What about the starving
beggars? What about the political
instability and the chance to eat
insects? I don't want foreign! Have you
seen the news lately, Philistine? Well, if
you want exotic, go to Hawaii! They still
trade in beads there and ride planks
rather than motorboats. Time for me to
head south again. On the next show, we'll
be discussing:
Amsterdam: Paradise Regained?
Morocco: Squidgy Smoke? Until next time,
travel safe. Ciao, bella! I'm James Piston
and this has been The Wild
Traveler.
This is WCTR, committed to
bringing you shows like The Wild
Traveler, even if we received a cease
and desist. Let's head over to the newsroom.
Lianne Forget for WCTR News, reporting what the
morning memo tells us to. Pornography in
preschool, the sickening shortage in
shiny compact discs turning your
children into killers. Plus, the Epsilon
Tract: a psychotic underground, power-
hungry cult running the government and
Vinewood, or an idea whose time has come?
The WCTR team spoke to one member:
"Whenever I'm in trouble, I talk to my
invisible friends. When I was a kid, my
mother told me to be good, or invisible
people would kill me. I'm passing that
terrifying living lie along to my children
like a virus." Also, police are investigating
the murder of Liberty City crime family
the Sindaccos, whose bodies were found in a
meat factory in Las Venturas. Could this
be the start of a mafia war, or was it a
sick game gone hideously wrong? Either
way, America's beef producers say it will
all blow over. Los Santos police officers
Frank Tenpenny and Eddie Pulaski are
being sought by government officials in
order to stand trial for the murder of
Officer Ralph Pendelbury. The pair, whom
prosecutors claim have masterminded a
huge criminal organization, have
disappeared. LSPD spokespeople said they
were undercover. Las Venturas was
recently celebrating the opening of The
Four Dragons Casino, a huge new pleasure
palace with a Chinese feel, setting a new
level of optimistic debauchery for the
country. Richard reports from Venturas,
where The Four Dragons hosted the Child
Actor Convention.
"Who do you have to [censored] to get a free drink in this place?"
"How do you stay 14 when the dealer's
showing 12, you [censored]?" "Yeah, hit me!" Richard?
Lianne, as you know, actors are a shallow
and insecure lot, often uncomfortable
with their sexuality, but what's worse
are child actors, especially when they
get together. Jimmy, from the canceled
sitcom Just the Five of Us, was dragged
out by police earlier today.
"This is [censored]! Hey, don't arrest my [censored]! I
am a star! It's just flour, I swear!" Jimmy,
I'm Richard Burns, WCTR News. What do you
think of My Five Uncles, the show that
replaced yours? "What do you think, dumbass?
That show sucks my ass!" And why do you
still look like a kid? "I'm 51 years old! I
just look like a kid! I'm going to [censored]
punch you!" Hey, how do you like that, you
liberal media bastard? Richard Burns, WCTR
News. Back to you, Lianne. I'm Lianne Forget
for WCTR News. I wouldn't sleep if I were you.
The Tight End Zone is next, brought to
you by Logger Beer and Redwood
Cigarettes. A game just isn't a game if
you're not drunk and coughing.
One, two... Goddamn, I think I just [censored] my pants!
You're now in The Tight End Zone. If
someone's playing with a ball or two,
we're there to talk about it. I'm your
host, Derrick Thackery. Today on the Big Show:
clearing out more housing projects for
golf courses, girls in skirts, and we
revisit the rivalry—the rivalry that
never dies! Liberty City Cocks and
Beavers going at it again! Love it, loathe
it, buy the jersey, eat the junk food, call
it athletics! I'm Derrick Thackery. Grab your
balls and run, 'cause someone is going to
pin you to the ground and give it up the
[censored]! Nowhere, Winner Takes All, including the J
& A Warts. Who is on the line?
Why don't you boys ever talk about the real issue in
sports today? The loss of tradition! I
wore a leather helmet playing football.
The left side of my face is paralyzed,
but it was worth it—we won the game! I
mean, my boy goes to high school, right?
And he's actually given a choice of
different sports to play, and there's
only one sport I know. It's ruining this
country's traditions and history. I mean,
I want him to be a big sports star so I
don't have to work no more, and he can
afford all the drugs and hookers he
wants! And he's only gone and started
playing lacrosse! Ooh, look at me, I'm
carrying my bag on a stick and wearing a
skirt! Might as well teach my boy to hunt
butterflies!
Okay, I guess you're right. Or wrong—it
all depends how you look at things. Any race
fans out there? Hey, any football fans? Soccer
fans, go home, we don't want you here! Your
game is terrible and we don't win at it!
Next caller.
Hi, Derrick, my name's Cole, and I'm a big racing fan.
I tell you that where I'm from, there's
nothing more exciting than getting
shit-faced and going deaf in 110-degree heat
and watching cars go in a circle for
several hours! Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, I think that's what it's all about. Huh, that and
putting a lot of stickers on your car, buddy.
Yeah, that really gets on my nerves. I
mean, I'm a bald man, my wife left me
because of it, and half the cars are
sponsored by baldness remedies! Castron
Team Racing... Yeah, wasn't the name of my
mother's cat! What's that all about? I mean,
racing teams should be sponsored by
things that are family-friendly, like hard
liquor or cigarettes, not the reason my
wife ran off with that cop! What...
Hey, screw your wife, pal! Probably a lot of
guys did! This ain't Lonely Hearts. I
mean, let's stop showering each other in
golden sports drink and get... get this
ball back in play! Hello, caller!
Derrick, that caller talking about the biathlon...
It's sick, I tell you, and unnatural! This
town has never been the same since they
had the Olympics here years ago. Kids
flinging javelins like ancient Greeks,
people running with burning torches,
throwing hammers. What kind of man wakes
up in the morning and says, "I'm going to
go throw hammers for a living"? Ooh, the
long jump! "Look at me, I can jump really
high!" Great, I have a gun, want to fight?
It's distracting us from our primal urge
to paint your face with war paint, whip
yourself into a sweaty, chaotic frenzy, and
then go annihilate and hospitalize
complete strangers. Then you bang a bimbo
on the
sidelines. Bang, bang, bang! Look, I loved
high school football and I love
gymnastics. Hey, Jack from Idlewood in Los
Santos. Yeah, how come you don't talk
about the best sport of all: horse racing?
I mean, tiny, angry people on horses. How
can you go wrong? I don't ride anything
bigger than me, you know what I'm saying?
I mean, that's why I've never been in a rodeo, man.
I mean, first off, why would you ride a
bull? Go find a big girl. They—they—they—
they could use the attention, and—and
that's all we have time for, okay? Hey, I'm
Derek Zakary. Till next time, play safe,
people. Go baby go
team. You're listening to WCTR. Or maybe
you aren't. Maybe you became so offended
that The Tight End Zone has no female
callers that you changed stations. I know
I would, and have. I'm not here anymore,
pompous. I'm running on air, I'm walking on
clouds. I don't exercise, I don't care,
pompous. I paid top dollar for these
incredible, high-technology polyester
shoes to walk around the mall and shop
for more sports equipment I won't play
sports in. I need to get more from life.
Much more. I need to get high, really high.
High on
air. Oh yeah, these Eris shoes really pump
up! That's right, you can now buy some air!
The science of sports and marketing
results in a shoe that pumps. Sound silly
to you? What if we told you that Eris
Pump Up would improve your game by 300%?
But I don't have a game. You got to have
game! Be a winner, pump up, and slam
dunk! Oh yeah! Guard the size of your shoes!
You'll shave seconds off your personal
best. Oh yeah! You mean I can whack off
even more times a day? Absolutely!
Probably five times more, because you'll
be walking on air! You'll feel so much
more athletic! After pumping up your
shoes, you'll automatically lose weight
and feel high-tech, just like the sports
stars! You are a star now! You're a winner
with air in his shoes! Now I can reach
for the stars! I've pumped up my
ego! Pump it, pump it up with
Eris! Turn over in case you learn
something. The news is next. Lianne for WCTR
News, unfair and skewed for you. In the
top stories: everyone is trying to kill
you, but at least you're not in prison
yet. Disgraced movie star Jack Howitzer
broke his silence recently following his
on-air murder of radio host Billy Dexter.
Facing trial and a possible death
sentence, Howitzer spoke to Richard.
WCTR would like to be clear, we did pay
for this interview. That's right, Lianne. I
am Richard Burns, here in Los Santos
Prison. As we all know, since politicians
stopped musicians from coming here to
sing songs about shooting your woman on
drugs, everyone is now questioning their
sexuality. Jack Howitzer, you're facing a
death sentence. How do you feel about
that? I broke out of a POW camp in Korea,
all right? So I'll be out of here soon. Uh,
correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe
that was a movie, and it wasn't real. Oh
no, it was real! I'm a veteran of over 40
films, but I've got a different hoochie
now. Say hello to the newsman, Hoochie. Um,
hello. You want me to kill you like the
last hoochie? Say it like an Asian girl! Uh,
hello, how are you? Wow, Jack Howitzer, that
is a fine prison bitch. Where can I get
one of those? Richard "BD" Burns, WCTR News.
The trial of allegedly disgraced police
officers Frank Tenpenny and Eddie
Pulaski began yesterday. Although Mr.
Pulaski was not at court personally,
prosecutors maintain both are guilty of
murder, racketeering, drug running, and
sexual offenses. Defense maintained
officers were just doing their job.
Government officials are denying any
knowledge of black helicopters that were
recently seen flying over the state.
Black helicopters? What black helicopters?
That cleared that up. A Las Venturas
institution, Caligula's, forced to admit
that it was recently robbed. It's the
first major heist carried out on a
Venturas casino in 30 years. Government
officials are not ruling out foul play.
Meanwhile, no explanation has been
forthcoming as to why the Sherman Dam
stopped generating electricity for a few
hours recently. One bystander blamed
aliens who drink electricity before
deflowering virgins. I'm Lianne for WCTR
News. It's going to get worse, trust me.
Your home is your castle, and like most
castles, there's always the worrisome
less fortunate trying to storm the gates.
No longer! At Executive Intruder
Extermination Service, we'll ensure
that you'll live in a fortress and live
your life worry-free. With my vindictive
and backstabbing personality, I always
knew I'd be successful, but there's a
price to pay. Money gives me freedom—
freedom to be scared of things that
normal people don't have to worry about.
When it comes to people trying to get a
buck off me or come knocking, I turn to
outside help. Your home will be
surrounded by only the best security
equipment: razor wire, Dobermans, landmines,
night vision, and motion sensors. And if a
stranger or unwanted relative should
make it inside, all of your doors will be
wired with bombs. But what about when my
children need to go to school? Your
children will be equipped with
bulletproof vests and, depending on if
they attend public school, stun guns and
mace. When you're successful, nobody wants
to be bothered. I'll slaughter anyone who
even thinks of harming my family. With
Executive Intruder Extermination Service,
they do it for me. Call today for your
free home demonstration. The world is a
dangerous place. For you, it doesn't have
to be. Enjoy listening to mental patients.
Area 53 is next. Is your child really an
alien? Has the future already happened
somewhere else? And finally, is cheese the
latest weapon in a battle against
communism? We explore deeper... much deeper.
I'm Marvin Trill. This is Area 53.
Prepare to be appalled. Hello? Yes, hello, I would like
to talk about a conspiracy. Okay, it
starts with food and our toxic culture.
These chemicals in our bodies, you must
flush them out, Marvin. First, start by
masticating... Did you say masturbating?
Listen again, Marvin. Am I lisping here?
Masticating vigorously. To really cleanse,
you're going to have to do some yoga. The
cleansing properties of doing yoga with
a garden hose up your ass cannot be
exaggerated, Marvin. It's time for your
down-dog to really have a tail. I was
wondering when my career would hit
bottom, and now it's here, right before my
eyes. Stewart is on the line. I think
everyone out there will agree that the
Russians are in charge now. Foreigners
are behind that EXORO handheld gaming
device to decrease our productivity and
make our thumbs useless so our kids
can't fire machine guns. I hear what
you're saying about video games. People
are dying every day of malaria, and it's
all because of the messages planted in
our minds from that Degenatron in the '80s.
Line 18. Hello. Okay, man, I warned you.
I've been over to the other side. What are you
talking about, buddy? I've been inside,
inside everything, seen everything.
Remember the first time you did
mushrooms? There are aliens living in the
state, aliens, and I've held them in my
own hand. Everybody, go to the desert, beg
their forgiveness! And how do you know
all this? I went to the camp! Believe what
you want to believe, but ask yourself, why
should I make this up? The only thing I
want to ask myself is how I can keep you
off future shows. Oh God. Kevin, hello,
you're on the air. All the missiles are
under my control, not the government's
control. Why do you think they put me in
solitary confinement for eight months?
Because I can launch nuclear
missiles by just whistling into a phone.
Really? Great. Could you wipe out all the
other radio stations in town for me? Hey,
I don't do that anymore. I only use my
powers for good. Ah, look, this isn't a
cartoon or TV show. Let's get real for a
second. The problem with people like you
who have superpowers is that you really
don't use them for good. If I had
superpowers, everyone would be naked, and
women signing autographs at conventions
couldn't resist me. All right, going to
the conspiracy line. Yeah, this—this is
Montag, okay? My name's Montag. Oh yes, yes,
I got that. Hey, have you ever leveled a
house with a helicopter? Yeah, no, but
that'd be really cool. I thought you were
a DJ. You used to talk more about killing
people with helicopters. I prefer
electric cable, tightly wound around
people's throats, watching them go blue
in the face. We have a lot of aerospace
fans and plenty of murderers who like
the show. Inside, I feel like it's time to
close the pod bay door and take a rest.
Until next time, reset your memory chip,
and don't—don't believe what they tell
you. This is Marvin Trill. You're leaving
Area 53. God bless and be
careful. That was Area 53, where reality
is an alien concept. If you crave news:
WCTR, West Coast Talk
Radio. [Music]
Sounds like you got a nasty cough. Yeah, no shit.
Here, baby, try this. Soothe? Yeah,
Soothe. Annihilates cough and cold
symptoms.
Wow, I'm seeing
donkeys! That's the patented cough-
killing concoction of codeine, morphine,
and alcohol. Your cold will be history.
How's your cold now? Who the hell are you?
I'm your wife, fool! Soothe kills a cough
fast. And for the kids' chesty cough, it's
Soothe Junior, the medication that comes in a
fun, animal-shaped container kids will
love! "Hey, look at me! I'm taking medication
just like
Dad!" Oh my God, he's bleeding! No, that—that's
just the medicine doing its magic. Thanks
to Soothe, his cough is history. With Soothe,
you'll forget you had a cough, your name,
or where to properly go to the bathroom.
Feel better fast with
Soothe. Now it's the couple who each
thinks the other is screwing America.
I Say, You Say is next with the
Phillipses. I'm Dr. Phillips, and I'm a
liberal. Get to a 10-step program! That's
12 steps. Yeah, you only deserve 10! I'm
also Dr. Phillips, and I'm conservative.
Today on the show: is it okay to talk to
people we were at war with once? And the
skyrocketing price of buying off a
politician! And we talk to people without
healthcare who are genuinely happy not
to be burdened with it. It's political
debate and discussion from the right and
the wrong side of the tracks. Let's go to
the phones before right-wing anger
engulfs my wife. Who's on the line? Hi, I
have an eating disorder, so I like moved
to the West Coast. Oh, that's so sad. Maybe
you need a support group with some
caring friends. Yeah, maybe you should
keep your finger out of your throat and
eat a donut! 99% of the world wake up
each day and eat dirt, and Queen Puke-a-Lot
here can't keep a meal down! Boohoo!
What do you expect, sympathy? This is Los
Santos, people would give their right arm
and left leg to live here. It's paradise,
but you have to suffer to belong. If you
can't take the heat, get out of the
nuclear reactor! Next caller. Yeah, uh, I
agree with that caller about the nuclear
plant next to the projects, you know.
Nature has a way of taking care of poor
people. Tornadoes don't like poor people,
right? Like, I don't do laundry. I'm
liberated, independent, and I have three
maids, all of them on less than minimum
wage. I mean, poor people are so happy to
work for me, especially when I help them
unionize uh do you have a question sort
of hey you know I got the same name as
you yeah pton oh well it's a family name
no Mary I was called Bruce by my parents
but I prefer Mary it's much more yeah
feminine no biblical which like okay I'm
an atheist but I love the Bible I have
aund that I took from hotel rooms what's
your question well as a mother and a
fireman I was wondering what you guys
thought about diversity in America it
makes me very nervous well you see I'm
heavily into diversity I'm like a a man
with a womb lactating yes I think you're
a little confused no you're the one
that's confused I'm the one who eats
Alaskan salmon and children from Alabama
I speak English I eat German food I
practice French adultery and I weigh as
much as Vatican City I'm an American
okay you're a nut get off our show Mary
would you please stop eyeing the
producer I already slept with him so did
I O Brian's on the line hello Brian hi
my name's Brian I work at cigalus casino
in Las Venturas excellent you take
stupid people's money I love it very
capitalist hey Brian what's your concern
I did really well in the 80s but the
'90s are proving to be a real drag the
music is terrible the recession is
kicking my ass everyone I know is giv up
recreational drug use and the president
is doing my head in the 80s were really
a materialistic time I know I'm a
shallow person drown me look we need a
movie star to be president it works
they're the best Liars they do it
professionally well so do all
politicians next caller yeah I want to
talk about deforestation yes that is a
shame what they're doing to the thick
beautiful redwoods North of San Vio I
was talking about women but you're right
Sano is half the problem it ain't
natural and it's unamerican look
infatuation and disillusionment is the
American way but it works just look at
places without professional wrestling in
porno porno is the exploitation of women
some people want to be exploited like
Factory workers others want to be
degraded I mean really really degraded
like a liberal having his way with you
god it makes me feel so dirty talk more
slowly please dear moving swiftly on
from my wife you're an I say you say and
what's your question yeah this is Brad
I'm really into pleasuring myself good
grief well that's my business but I feel
discriminated against not only can I not
practice my hobby in the privacy of my
own Garden or car but my movies are
rated as
pornographic I mean let me ask you a
question thre sums right well that's
where our problem started yeah the
producer well right I ran a movie with
two chicks and a dude and it's called a
porno people look at me like I'm some
sort of creep but it's natural but I
rent a movie with two dudes and a chick
it's all in French probably wins awards
called an art housee love triangle but
it's revolting no you're revolting get
the airwaves and into therapy buddy oh
that's the problem with men you're
imbeciles and yet you married me God
don't rub it in I did I was desperate
that's all we have time for luckily this
show is headed downhill when you take
the worst qualities of an elephant and a
donkey you get a lot of [ __ ] we'll see
you next time on I say you say you said
you like me in that donkey suit
jackass I say you say is heard only on
wct be thankful next up the reason
you're afraid the news Leanne for wct
news reporting what makes the
administration happy today's top stories
do trees cause baldness is noise the new
silent enemy of your family and a
special report on France one nation's
obsession with standup toilets breaking
wct news Navy officials are denying that
a hydrop plane was stolen from a Marine
Amphibious assault ship recently despite
eyewitness reports to the contrary
taxpayers on the scene are not happy I
pay my taxes that jet is supposed to be
bombing school and the FBI is
investigating possible links between the
massacre of farelli family members and
the slaying of the sndo family
unconfirmed reports suggest a similar
style of execution was used in both hits
an official commented it could be a
wormhole in space I'm Leanne for wct
news don't turn it off trust
me the most boring show with a brand new
host entertaining America with llo
welcome to entertaining America on wct
with me llo so the media you may hate us
but I got to tell you we hate ourselves
more and stop accusing us of being
liberal what a load of crap this station
is owned by ammunation I mean have you
ever heard anyone complain about guns on
this station hosts are getting shot by
them all the time but it just gets
glossed over but it also means I I now
have a job if you're afraid of your
mortality and never want to die here's
the solution it's a man who's got all of
America talking with his unique approach
to spiritual matters he's helped
thousands or so the Press pack tells me
Chris forage founder of the Epsilon
program is here hello Chris klam brother
brother what does that mean man so
epsilonism is it a load of crap or is it
the future well what do you think llo I
don't know well I mean I I I grow my own
religion is why I don't know it's I'm
kind of spaced out I mean but you guys
run around chanting lip bomb it's klom
well whatever both sound addictive to me
you know only popular people are
addicted to either let's go to the
phones hey Chris Epsilon sounds awesome
but if you read the fossil records
hunter gatherer dudes had it made I mean
who wouldn't want to drag their women
around by their hair they smoked
anything they could find that's like so
freaking cool then all the men would
like disappear for days at a time and
you'd only hear Beast shrieking in the
distance you know I went to a museum
once that guy got a point points are
irrelevant llo let me ask you something
do you want to be happy llo what kind of
question is that yes obviously then why
do you marck the happiness of others
well I mean this is Vinewood we're all
supposed to be like psychotic and Dogg
eat dog and you know bang your best
friend's wife I mean I'm with that last
guy we all have a primitive side there
Chris I mean you should have heard the
music I used to like in the'80s it was
it was hysterical what's hysterical
about being descended from from a sponge
and not knowing it what's funny about
being told that the world is millions of
years old when in fact it's only 157
years old fact and its age does not
change there's nothing funny about that
it's just weird you know that voice of
yours man holy [ __ ] I can believe
anything you say my time has come llo
and so has yours if if you let it um
well you know that that sounds good to
me hey wait are you going to try to sign
me up for the military that happened
once before I mean I'm into killing
people and I can say I'm cry when I'm
done killing and then there listen my
friend you can mock but I know the truth
about you I can see past your jokes into
that scared little boy beneath you you
my friend like a lot of other people are
being lined to I totally agree with you
finally inversion therapy I owe my mom a
huge apology listen pick a new set of
Lies mine are better let me ask you
something when did you last get laid llo
speaking of Lies wait look I'm not an
egg I got laid this morning by twins
whoa they each laid an egg and I formed
out of them what are you talking about
great a horny cult leader with a
breakfast fixation I love it you know
I'm thinking of a cult centered around
grits oh wait I'm sorry there already is
one in it's called the south for the
last time this is not a cult llo it's a
fellowship of like-minded adults who
tithe money in exchange for salvation
and merit badges every single thing we
do is voluntary including the swinging
and making things up why is this whole
town obsessed with
swinging let's go to the phones hey llo
love the show man hey I really love to
make out with hot chicks in church
perfect join us we've put a price on
salvation and it's a price worth paying
believe me look if you crave sexual
Conquest family betrayal class Warfare
and really feeling like you are a part
of something then just do it just do it
it's so easy join the Epsilon
group Chris stop trying to recruit
people I mean you even say you just make
this stuff up let's go to the phones hi
la llo ah Darius Fontaine look I told
you to leave me alone look look it was
an unfortunate incident that happened to
your mother but I was quite clear
grandmother not mother it's your fault
it doesn't work I nearly went to prison
man what you told me to do is illegal in
Most states whatever look Chris forage
is a liar and a cheat he made it up it
doesn't help anyone apart from him the
fact is people need to face their fears
remember I always say that face your
fears Don't Run Away Darius Fontaine can
kill my ass oh you you'd like that would
would you like that I don't think so and
I'll tell you why because you are the
devil people aren't really afraid you
know yet you make them kill their
families fears have to be faced that's
what I always say just ask llo hey don't
bring me into this Ruckus Darius this is
between you two guacos I mean and you
stay away from me Darius I've got a
restraining order dude llo the only way
that you can really communicate with
your ancestor aners is to pay someone
like me just a second I want you to try
something touch my cane this whole town
man I I think you've seen too many
movies dude you can be happy listen join
us be famous find your true self have a
breast nose surgery whatever you want
lie with nine new partners a week it
explains everything if there are no
women make them from sand from garbage
out of thin there the rich cry too low
well that's an interesting theory that
sounds like it was formulated with
Pharmaceuticals but you know I would
like to find about being rich and crying
cuz right now I'm just poor and crying
but this is the West Coast you know I'm
only in a lesbians man it's Destiny
Vinewood only lets you down in the
Epsilon program there are no series
finales it goes on and on and on we
don't abandon you H well we're going to
have to abandon this show great my first
show when a dude nearly kills me now I'm
being harassed by a former sociology
professor and an alcoholic turned self
deifying cultist please I got to get
back to the east coast this has been
entertaining America with llo on wct
culturally this country is flatlining
now you know why your home is your
castle and like most castles there's
always the worrisome less fortunate
trying to storm the gates no longer an
executive Intruder extermination service
we'll ensure that you'll live in a
fortress and live your life WorryFree
with my vindictive and backstabbing
personality I always knew I'd be
successful but there's a price to pay
money gives me freedom freedom to be
scared of things that normal people
don't have to worry about when it comes
to people trying to get a buck off me or
come knocking I turn to outside help
your home will be surrounded by only the
best security equipment razor wire Dober
mins landmines night vision and motion
sensors and if a stranger or unwanted
relative should make it inside all of
your doors will be wired with bombs but
what about when my children need to go
to school your children will be equipped
with bulletproof vests and depending on
if they attend public school stun guns
and mace when you're successful nobody
wants to be bothered I'll Slaughter
anyone who even thinks of harming my
family with executive Intruder
extermination service, they do it for me.
Call today for your free home
demonstration! The world is a dangerous
place for you, it doesn't have to
be! Breaking WCTR News: we go to Richard in
Los
Santos. Dude, I am shitfaced! Line--
Los Santos is in flames! This riot is
spectacular, man! I mean, I can't even
describe it. Storefronts are being
smashed everywhere! There is some great
stuff to be had! There is free beer for
everybody, dude! I've been loading up. This
is capitalism as it was meant to be, baby!
Hey! Hey, get away from my news van! Yeah,
that's right, I'm packing heat! I'm Richard
Burns, shit! Uh, police advisor, state of
martial law has been declared. You should
stay in your home! Senators are burning
the Constitution, blah blah bitty bloo blah
blah blah. I'm Richard Burns,
WCTR
News. Jimmy! Jimmy, get me some more beer
out of the back of the van, and clear out
some space. We're going to get ourselves
a big screen! We'll keep you posted. Now
back to regular programming.
Hello, Lisa. Yeah, how you doing, bitch? How
do you like living in that house we
built together, huh? Do our kids like
watching that bald bastard of a new
husband kiss you in the morning? They
want their real father, Lisa! When you
just can't be there in person, San
Andreas Telephone: for those difficult
conversations. Lonely? It's about to get
much worse! Lonely Hearts is next. I'm
Christy McIntyre, and this is Lonely
Hearts. Hearts, you know, when we get
dumped or minimized, it's really a good
thing, because really... I want you to
listen to me! Pull over! I said pull over!
Life is not a game, life is love. First
caller. Jez, remember me? I told you, leave
me alone! Sometimes the heart is
confusing, lady! So is the brain, you talk
too much! If you look out the window, you
will notice your car is on fire! Oh my
God, Fernando is back! Women know nothing
about
love! This is why I am here. Fernando
grows tired of hearing women on the
radio with bad advice, because if you
close your eyes, you can be loving anyone,
especially when you are alone in an
airplane bathroom, and people are
knocking on the door, and you keep
flushing and flushing. Let's take a goer
whose heart is on the line. Love is
finally in the air! Hi, I love the show.
I'm in a great mood, my mistress just got
her period! I love that day. Anyway, I love
my wife, I have 18 children, and-- Why do you
have so many children? Are you a man with
a fire in his loins and a hole in his
Johnny? Well, I can't really talk about
that. I'm passing on a tradition, raising
little soldiers. Tsk, you sound like you
enjoy the fetal position and sucking your
thumb! Wow, how'd you know? I always know.
It's fine, Fernando loves to suck his, too.
It's so hot and sexy. People, love
yourself first, and then focus on others.
You are number one, your spouse is number
two, and in the ultimate scenario, they're
number three, and number two comes from
Las Venturas' phone book after you see
Fernando's ad in the classifieds! Maybe we
leave that for now, amigos. Line eight,
Daisy, you're on the new and improved
Lonely Hearts, Fernando Martinez speaking.
Speaking of number two, I totally love my
boyfriend, but like, the skid marks, I
don't know what to do. Yes, cars and pants
have a lot in common! A real man leaves
his mark like a stallion. But I mean, I
smell it, but I don't say anything, and he
just rolls down the window and acts like
it's all cool. Well, it's not cool! Why do
men have this problem? Fernando learned
this years ago while playing emotional
music. Inside every great man is a
wounded little boy, full of fire! Fire
from his ass, climbing trees, blowing up
frogs, beating up slow classmates,
sleeping with your friends, all in a
day's work! It is life, it is love, it is
better than warts, I think. On line four
is a guy who calls himself
Carpenter Chris. Hell yeah! I'm a
carpenter. I drink all day and nail 2x4s!
Oh, yes, little people need love more than
anyone! I have one client who calls me
all the time, the girls complain he's
stuck in the '70s. Let's take another call,
Fernando is in charge, riding the phone
like a cheap whore! Line six, hi! I've got a
very extensive pornography collection, it
takes up the whole house. What does that
say about me? It says what somebody
should say. Maybe I say it. Listen to
Fernando! There is nothing like the real
thing. It is so silly to spend hundreds
of dollars on videotapes of people
making passion when you can make the
tapes yourself, and sell them, and make
money! Let Fernando heal you like a
chiropractor, but not as creepy and
addictive. Hello, Frank from Foster Valley.
I wish my dog could talk and cuddle me
all night. Ew! Stay away from animals!
It's-- it's not legal, not even for me. It
is not moral. Maybe someday I set up a
petting zoo for people like you. When
you want to understand the connection
that keeps us on this planet since the
dinosaurs, when the passion burns like a
nasty itch, when fate caused you to leave a
town after an incident, or the risk of a
father's shotgun... Is fate an incident? Is a
five-alarm fire an incident? I come to
Las Venturas, a city with more love than
it can handle. Love is realizing your
calling. I say this: I once played music
that brings back passion, but I realize you
can have even more passion with a credit
card. People in Venturas only care about
slot machines. Yes, maybe you pull the
handle and win the backdoor passion. It
is different with every woman. Some women
need the soft touch because they have
been traumatized. Others have already
been traumatized, so you treat them like
a truck driver and steal a six-pack on
your way out! What are you talking about?
I am talking about passion! I am talking
about romance! Hey, let me back in, it's my
show! No, I teach you how to talk in just
a second... To be quiet! Goodbye, ladies and
gentlemen, it is so good to teach you
about love. San Andreas, you in your car, touch
yourself, I love you all! Christy, I will
be out in five, wear something slinky, but
sophisticated and trashy. Your heart is
no longer lonely, Fernando has been here.
This was Lonely Hearts. Get out of here,
you creep! Oh my God, is that Bouchon Cologne
you're wearing? Yes, that is Bouchon Cologne. Do
you like that? And do you like this? This
is Fernando's signature move.
Fernando, that Latin passion is amazing! Oh
wow, that's incredible! Let me see that! I-- I love
taco, let me see that taco, please give it
to me!
Fernando-- That was Lonely Hearts, only on
WCTR. Talk is cheap, especially on this
station featuring more rich, angry people
complaining. WC-
-TR. And now the number one show for
vegetables on the radio, Gardening with
Maurice. Okay, we are back in the garden.
I'm Maurice, and we must answer Nature's
call. Going to the phones. Greetings,
garden lover, what's your name? Hi, my name
is Trish. Okay, is that short for Patricia?
Uh, yeah. Oh, then what I asked is what
your name was, not the nickname your skinhead,
boot-wearing friends call you at
the rallies. Maybe you should do less
drugs and learn to try a bit harder. Next
caller! Hi, my name is Colleen, and my
husband has a topiary problem. Ooh, this
sounds serious. Well, he started off small-
scale, just recreational usage, you know,
doing horses and shit, rams, the odd unicorn,
but it's kind of gotten out of control. Mm,
how so? He just can't stop. I mean, people
think it's all fun and games, but what
happens when the party stops? What
happens then? Okay, just-- just hold the
phone! Hold the phone and get a grip, okay?
At my house, when the party stops, we pay
the whore, get rid of the sailors, and 15
men start crying in unison. Well, that's
your business. My husband's reached
bottom. It's terrible! Giraffes, lions,
elephants, rhinos, all of them carved out
of hedges! Penguins, dogs, velociraptors,
you name it, he's made a leafy version.
What could be more natural than a
man trimming a hedge into the shape of
an animal? Very therapeutic. Makes a man
feel like a god. When you can twist
nature to your own perverse
entertainment, then you know we've won.
Eat me, Darwin! But now he's trimming
bushes into a spaceship, a rocket, and a
lance. He runs around with hedge clippers
and screams, "Trim that bush!" at our
neighbors. He even fashioned a shrub into
a kangaroo with a pouch, and he sleeps
inside it at night. Oh, he's freaking out on
bush! He needs help, please, you got to
help me, I hate hedges! Well, the Romans
loved topiary, and look at their
contributions to society. But as they say,
"If the grass is greener in the other
fella's yard, then you bang his college
son when the dad's out of town." Okay, next
caller. Whoops! Hold on a second, I'm
blossoming. There we go, all done. My
name's Henry, I-- Are you blossoming? I, uh, I
guess I am. I've really come into my own
in the past few months since I joined a
cult and began tithing money in exchange
for spiritual happiness and letting
everyone take turns on my wife. Anyway, I
have a lovely garden, mostly carnivorous
plants. A Venus flytrap reminds me of my
mother; she's in prison now. Anyway, it's
so fascinating how it catches animals
and eats them. I started with flies, and
now mine can swallow a whole squirrel or
a small horse if I cut it in half first.
Have you tried any experiments on human
beings? Yeah, I've been working on that.
Good man, good man. See, the secret of
nature is once something is at the
height of beauty and potential, it is
time for it to wither and die. A bit like
the British Empire, 'cause look at that
whole place withering and dying right
before our eyes. It's run by a queen, and
if she had a pistol, she'd be the king.
Luckily, in this country, we don't know
the meaning of the word hubris. But hell,
I'm all over the place here! It's so easy
to get out of control when you're doing
something that comes natural. Line two,
you're on Gardening with Maurice. Yeah, my
name is Terence. Can I call you Telly
Welly? Well, uh, sure. I-- I guess. I'm growing
flowers, but sometimes I get really angry
and fly off the handle, commit herbicide.
I don't mean to. I say, "I didn't mean it,
baby, you'll be all right." Then I cry and
wear a diaper for two days. A flower is
nothing more than an educated weed,
and like all weeds, all living things
need to be extinguished. Like a life
support machine, or-- or a cigarette, which
I won't be able to smoke anymore if the
fascists in the state government have
anything to say about it with that damn
Proposition 421! Tobacco is a plant,
people! And, and, and if it comes out of
the ground, we should be able to smoke it,
like coal and opium! Next caller. Yeah, I
got a question: why is everybody on the
radio named Maurice? God, I pray to the
Great Gardener in the sky that you've
been fixed. I hope they snipped your nuts
off, because spreading your seed could be
a disaster. Do you-- do you have a question?
A question? God, so many vegetables on
this show. Tards. Yeah, that guy was
talking about bugs and plants that eat
them. I got a better solution: put
pesticide in the sprinklers. My kids love
it. I mean, the ones that lived. Oh, lovely,
you're a lovely human being! You fucking
imbecile! You morons in this town are
spreading like weeds, like little bastard
dandelions! I wish I could just pop every
one of your goddamn heads off! Hello,
line eight, you're on Gardening with Maurice.
Yeah, I heard what you said about bonsai
trees, and you know what? You can stick
that green thumb right up your
ass! Yes, another man who grows miniature
plants so he can feel like a giant. A
real man loves enormous trees that he
can
have his way with, chopping them down and
using the wood to fashion rocking horses
and-- and suggestive whirligigs. Okay,
we're running out of time, literally. But
again, like a seed sown in a hurricane or
a mushroom spore from outer space, the
garden goes on. I'm Maurice, until next
Time to dig a hole and plant
yourself. That was the show that
generates more phone calls than any
other on WCTR, Gardening with Maurice. If
only the world was less like this: "I
could use a smoke." "Hey, put that out!" ...and
more like this: "I could use a smoke." "You
murderer! I might have children one day!"
Smoking kills, unless you kill first. If
you're around a smoker, you will die.
Smokers may look relaxed and like
they're having fun — don't believe it. Vote
"Yes" on Proposition 421. Let's outlaw
smoking everywhere, even in people's
homes, and allow honest citizens to legally kill
anyone who smokes. Let's live in a world
without smokers. Prohibition works, let's
prove it! Let's move up the food chain!
It's time to smoke the smokers. Vote "Yes"
on Proposition
421! Want to be too scared to go outside?
The news is next. Lianne Forget for WCTR State
Controlled News. Propped up breaking news:
Is skateboarding making your son
impotent, and how to find out? Today's top
stories: Why hatred is good for you,
foreigners worse than we thought, and our
top story concerns the death of recently
cleared police officer Frank Tenpenny.
His body was found in the aftermath of
the recent riot set off by his acquittal.
Coroners took several days to identify
the body, which had been mutilated and
stripped by the homeless. More on the
riot of the century: How do we keep it
from happening again? Richard is on the
streets with rescue
workers. Lianne, I don't know if you've
ever covered a riot,
but the scene here is
amazing! Rescue workers are opening up a
car with the Jaws of Life right here! It
is so cool! "I'm on fire!" Hey, shut up, [ __ ]!
I'm interviewing! What? You're ruining
my report, shut up! Hey, hey, rescue guy,
come here, come here! Richard Burns, WCTR
News. How's it going? "You dumbass, I'm
trying to save this woman, get out of
here!" I'm trying to save this woman... "That
bag!" Yeah, we'll see if I give you any
beers from my news truck, you overpaid
prick. Lianne, this town is going to need
some healing. Back to
you. "Hey, why don't you use the Jaws of
Life on your fat wife,
dude? Did you hear me rank him?" That was...
I'm so glad you're okay, Richard. "Hey, baby,
are we off the air? I looted some great
stuff for our apartment: a fat bearskin
rug, a new blender, a double-ender..."
Currently, we have no more information.
And in entertainment news, the comeback
of the year: disgraced drunkard Madd Dogg,
who was recently saved from jumping to
his death by a mystery assistant, is on
top of the charts with a new album and a
sellout tour planned. "Yes, people, the
wait is over! Madd Dogg is back on the
top where I belong, baby! Number one! Now, I
want to set the record straight at this
point. I've been hearing all kinds of
[ __ ] like I was drunk and I was on some
drugs and I had a breakdown or some [ __ ].
I was never in a hotel in Las
Venturas, that's [ __ ]! They're just
hating on a player, man. They been
hating on me since I was in baby shoes! I
was in the studio, yeah! Took a little
time off. I watched y'all rappers get out
there and try to do your thing, but now
I'm ready to drop this dog [ __ ] on your
wacky-ass rappers! I got a new manager,
his name is Carl Johnson, and we gonna
take this rap game to a new level, by
storm for the second time! Yeah, [ __ ]!
Sign up right now to get on my whole
roster! It's gonna be big, yeah! Get
in, take a number, hoe, take a number!"
Lianne Forget for WCTR News. This is the end, and
a new beginning.